<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <ARA_Incubator_Nutrient_Solution.label>Arachne nutrient solution</ARA_Incubator_Nutrient_Solution.label>
  <ARA_Incubator_Nutrient_Solution.description>The nutrient solution of the Arachne Zerg hatching tank, eggs and cocoons all need this liquid rich in various nutrients to maintain the progress of hatching.</ARA_Incubator_Nutrient_Solution.description>
  <ARA_Incubator_Nutrient_Solution.tools.0.label>water</ARA_Incubator_Nutrient_Solution.tools.0.label>
  <ARA_Pawn_Ootheca.label>Arachne oocysts</ARA_Pawn_Ootheca.label>
  <ARA_Pawn_Ootheca.description>A fragile, flammable, slimy sac that contains the nutrients and genetic material needed to nurture a new insect or beast insect. A spacious incubator filled with Arachne's nutrient solution will be the best place to place it. It needs to be entered by the Arachne Larvae to initiate the hatching process.</ARA_Pawn_Ootheca.description>
  <ARA_Pawn_Ootheca.comps.CompProperties_RefuelableNutrition.fuelGizmoLabel>insect honey</ARA_Pawn_Ootheca.comps.CompProperties_RefuelableNutrition.fuelGizmoLabel>
  <ARA_Pawn_Ootheca.comps.CompProperties_IncubatorData.buttonLabel>incubation···</ARA_Pawn_Ootheca.comps.CompProperties_IncubatorData.buttonLabel>
  <ARA_Pawn_Ootheca.comps.CompProperties_IncubatorData.buttonDesc>Select hatched Arachneid...</ARA_Pawn_Ootheca.comps.CompProperties_IncubatorData.buttonDesc>
  <ARA_Pawn_Ootheca.comps.CompProperties_IncubatorData.menuTitle>hatch menu</ARA_Pawn_Ootheca.comps.CompProperties_IncubatorData.menuTitle>
  <ARA_Equipment_Ootheca.label>Arachne cocoon</ARA_Equipment_Ootheca.label>
  <ARA_Equipment_Ootheca.description>The pagoda-like living structure of Arachne can hatch out incomplete individuals after metamorphosis - armed organs and fabrics, that is, the weapons and clothes of the insect swarm. It needs to be entered by the Arachne larvae to start the hatching process.一个宽敞、铺满阿拉克涅营养液的孵化间将是它最佳的放置场所。</ARA_Equipment_Ootheca.description>
  <ARA_Equipment_Ootheca.comps.CompProperties_RefuelableNutrition.fuelGizmoLabel>insect honey</ARA_Equipment_Ootheca.comps.CompProperties_RefuelableNutrition.fuelGizmoLabel>
  <ARA_InteractiveEggSac_Techprint.label>Arachne gene test egg</ARA_InteractiveEggSac_Techprint.label>
  <ARA_InteractiveEggSac_Techprint.description>An egg with almost disordered internal development cannot hatch any Zerg species and is mainly used for experimenting with the direction of mutation. \n\nArachne technology that requires a blueprint can only be completed by genetic test eggs. Multiple eggs can jointly research the same technology. When completed, the genetic information of the technology will be stored in the eggs. Once all the genetic test eggs storing the same technology are damaged, the technology will be lost!</ARA_InteractiveEggSac_Techprint.description>
  <ARA_BioforgeIncubator_Thing.label>Item hatching pool</ARA_BioforgeIncubator_Thing.label>
  <ARA_BioforgeIncubator_Thing.description>A large incubation facility that consumes a lot of nutrients can incubate multiple items at the same time and can increase efficiency by linking external equipment.</ARA_BioforgeIncubator_Thing.description>
  <ARA_BioforgeIncubator_Thing.comps.CompProperties_RefuelableNutrition.fuelGizmoLabel>insect honey</ARA_BioforgeIncubator_Thing.comps.CompProperties_RefuelableNutrition.fuelGizmoLabel>
  <ARA_BioforgeIncubator.label>Insect Hatching Pool</ARA_BioforgeIncubator.label>
  <ARA_BioforgeIncubator.description>A large, nutrient-intensive incubation facility can incubate multiple units at the same time, and can increase efficiency by linking external equipment.</ARA_BioforgeIncubator.description>
  <ARA_BioforgeIncubator.comps.CompProperties_RefuelableNutrition.fuelGizmoLabel>insect honey</ARA_BioforgeIncubator.comps.CompProperties_RefuelableNutrition.fuelGizmoLabel>
</LanguageData>
