<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>

  <ARA_MW_Bone_Sword.label>Armed Organ "Bone Blade"</ARA_MW_Bone_Sword.label>
  <ARA_MW_Bone_Sword.description>The basic melee armed organ used by the Arachnae Swarm Overseer Drone, connected to the drone's auxiliary limbs via multiple exposed nerve bundles. Although it is just a hard, sword-shaped bone plate, this in no way prevents the endlessly powerful Arachnae Swarm Overseer Drones from using it to decapitate every enemy that violates the hive.</ARA_MW_Bone_Sword.description>
  <ARA_MW_Bone_Sword.tools.0.label>pommel</ARA_MW_Bone_Sword.tools.0.label>
  <ARA_MW_Bone_Sword.tools.1.label>Sweep</ARA_MW_Bone_Sword.tools.1.label>

  <ARA_MW_Blade_Claw.label>Armed Organ "Carapace Blade Claw"</ARA_MW_Blade_Claw.label>
  <ARA_MW_Blade_Claw.description>An improved melee armed organ used by the Arachnae Swarm Overseer Drone, connected to the drone's auxiliary limbs via multiple exposed nerve bundles. Compared to the Bone Blade, it is made of lighter, sharper, and sturdier chitin, allowing for faster combat.</ARA_MW_Blade_Claw.description>
  <ARA_MW_Blade_Claw.tools.0.label>pommel</ARA_MW_Blade_Claw.tools.0.label>
  <ARA_MW_Blade_Claw.tools.1.label>Slice</ARA_MW_Blade_Claw.tools.1.label>

  <ARA_MW_Steel_Blade.label>Armed Organ "Refined Steel Blade"</ARA_MW_Steel_Blade.label>
  <ARA_MW_Steel_Blade.description>An advanced melee armed organ used by the Arachnae Swarm Overseer Drone, connected to the drone's auxiliary limbs via multiple exposed nerve bundles. Through the swarm's evolution, the drone is now able to use refined steel to strengthen the armed organ, making it sturdy and sharp.</ARA_MW_Steel_Blade.description>
  <ARA_MW_Steel_Blade.tools.0.label>pommel</ARA_MW_Steel_Blade.tools.0.label>
  <ARA_MW_Steel_Blade.tools.1.label>Steel Spike</ARA_MW_Steel_Blade.tools.1.label>

  <ARA_MW_Plasteel_Blade.label>Armed Organ "Plasteel Spike"</ARA_MW_Plasteel_Blade.label>
  <ARA_MW_Plasteel_Blade.description>An elite melee armed organ used by the Arachnae Swarm Overseer Drone, connected to the drone's auxiliary limbs via multiple exposed nerve bundles. Plasteel, being a sturdy and lightweight material, can significantly enhance the drone's melee capabilities.</ARA_MW_Plasteel_Blade.description>
  <ARA_MW_Plasteel_Blade.tools.0.label>pommel</ARA_MW_Plasteel_Blade.tools.0.label>
  <ARA_MW_Plasteel_Blade.tools.1.label>Plasteel Spike</ARA_MW_Plasteel_Blade.tools.1.label>

  <ARA_MW_Archotech_Blade.label>Armed Organ "Archotech Blade"</ARA_MW_Archotech_Blade.label>
  <ARA_MW_Archotech_Blade.description>The highest-tier melee armed organ used by the Arachnae Swarm Overseer Drone, connected to the drone's auxiliary limbs via multiple exposed nerve bundles. The Archotech Blade can drain life force from the attacked target and heal the drone during combat.</ARA_MW_Archotech_Blade.description>
  <ARA_MW_Archotech_Blade.tools.0.label>pommel</ARA_MW_Archotech_Blade.tools.0.label>
  <ARA_MW_Archotech_Blade.tools.1.label>Drain</ARA_MW_Archotech_Blade.tools.1.label>

  <ARA_Ranged_Needle.label>Armed Organ "Bone Needle"</ARA_Ranged_Needle.label>
  <ARA_Ranged_Needle.description>The basic ranged armed organ used by the Arachnae Swarm Overseer Drone, connected to the drone's auxiliary limbs via multiple exposed nerve bundles. The Bone Needle fires sharp bone spikes at distant enemies, though they lack accuracy.</ARA_Ranged_Needle.description>
  <ARA_Ranged_Needle.verbs.0.label>Bone Needle</ARA_Ranged_Needle.verbs.0.label>

  <ARA_Ranged_Acid.label>Armed Organ "Acid Sprayer"</ARA_Ranged_Acid.label>
  <ARA_Ranged_Acid.description>A ranged armed organ used by the Arachnae Swarm Overseer Drone, connected to the drone's auxiliary limbs via multiple exposed nerve bundles. It sprays concentrated acid at distant targets, capable of melting enemy armor.</ARA_Ranged_Acid.description>
  <ARA_Ranged_Acid.verbs.0.label>Acid Spray</ARA_Ranged_Acid.verbs.0.label>

  <ARA_Ranged_RefineNeedle.label>Armed Organ "Refined Bone Needle"</ARA_Ranged_RefineNeedle.label>
  <ARA_Ranged_RefineNeedle.description>An advanced ranged armed organ used by the Arachnae Swarm Overseer Drone, connected to the drone's auxiliary limbs via multiple exposed nerve bundles. The Refined Bone Needle fires processed bone spikes, which are more accurate than the basic version.</ARA_Ranged_RefineNeedle.description>
  <ARA_Ranged_RefineNeedle.verbs.0.label>Refined Bone Needle</ARA_Ranged_RefineNeedle.verbs.0.label>

  <ARA_Ranged_HeavyAcid.label>Armed Organ "Heavy Acid Sprayer"</ARA_Ranged_HeavyAcid.label>
  <ARA_Ranged_HeavyAcid.description>An elite ranged armed organ used by the Arachnae Swarm Overseer Drone, connected to the drone's auxiliary limbs via multiple exposed nerve bundles. It sprays concentrated acid at distant targets, capable of melting enemy armor. Compared to the basic Acid Sprayer, the Heavy Acid Sprayer sprays much more concentrated acid.</ARA_Ranged_HeavyAcid.description>
  <ARA_Ranged_HeavyAcid.verbs.0.label>Heavy Acid Spray</ARA_Ranged_HeavyAcid.verbs.0.label>

  <ARA_Ranged_ElectricBeam.label>Armed Organ "Archotech Beam Cannon"</ARA_Ranged_ElectricBeam.label>
  <ARA_Ranged_ElectricBeam.description>The highest-tier ranged armed organ used by the Arachnae Swarm Overseer Drone, connected to the drone's auxiliary limbs via multiple exposed nerve bundles. It can inflict powerful psychic damage on a single target from a great distance.</ARA_Ranged_ElectricBeam.description>
  <ARA_Ranged_ElectricBeam.verbs.0.label>Archotech Beam Cannon</ARA_Ranged_ElectricBeam.verbs.0.label>
  <ARA_Ranged_ElectricBeam.verbs.1.label>Archotech Beam Cannon Charging...</ARA_Ranged_ElectricBeam.verbs.1.label>

</LanguageData>