<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
<ARA_MimicNematodeShambler.label>Arachne pseudolinear parasite</ARA_MimicNematodeShambler.label>
<ARA_MimicNematodeShambler.description>Arachne pseudonematodes are one of the most mysterious branches of the insect family.Although they are of the same origin as the protozoan species, they did not develop advanced intelligence in the course of evolution and took a completely different path - parasitism.Pseudonematodes are parasitic species that cannot survive without a host. It is an insect. When it parasitizes an organism, it remains latent for a long time, and eventually takes control of the host's nervous system and metabolic system, turning it into a manipulated zombie-like "parasite." Due to its excellent cell replication and regeneration ability, the pseudolinear species However, this parasitic relationship is highly invasive; the eggs of the pseudonematode spread over the entire body surface of the parasite, and the organism attacked by the parasite becomes infected and eventually develops new It has the potential to become a parasite.Although the pseudoline species maintain the parasite's metabolism at a very low level, the parasite itself does not feed voluntarily, so it eventually ``deaths'' when it runs out of energy.</ARA_MimicNematodeShambler.description>
<ARA_MimicNematodeShambler.namePrefix>pseudolinear parasite</ARA_MimicNematodeShambler.namePrefix>
<ARA_MimicNematodeShambler.renderNodeProperties.0.debugLabel>shambler scar</ARA_MimicNematodeShambler.renderNodeProperties.0.debugLabel>
<ARA_MimicNematodeShambler.renderNodeProperties.1.debugLabel>shambler scar</ARA_MimicNematodeShambler.renderNodeProperties.1.debugLabel>
<ARA_MimicNematodeShambler.tools.0.label>Biting</ARA_MimicNematodeShambler.tools.0.label>
<ARA_MimicNematodeShambler.tools.1.label>giant sickle</ARA_MimicNematodeShambler.tools.1.label>
<ARA_MimicNematodeShambler.tools.2.label>giant sickle</ARA_MimicNematodeShambler.tools.2.label>
</LanguageData>
