<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <Arachnae_Queen_BS_Child_1.description>[PAWN_nameDef] is an Arachne zerg queen, born with hundreds of sisters and sealed in a breeding chamber. \n\nWhen the beeswax sealing the queen's breeding chamber was opened by the worker bees, [PAWN_nameDef] stood in the chamber - covered in blood and tissue fluid, with the broken limbs and bodies of the sisters under her feet - she was undoubtedly the only winner from the survival game.</Arachnae_Queen_BS_Child_1.description>
  <Arachnae_Queen_BS_Adult_1.description>After [PAWN_nameDef] successfully grew up in the insect nest, she left the nest where she was born and came to a strange area to prepare to establish her own power. \n\n[PAWN_nameDef] knows that she is weak and weak, so compared to other pampered sisters, she is more willing to do many things herself.</Arachnae_Queen_BS_Adult_1.description>
  <Arachnae_Node_BS_Child_1.description>[PAWN_nameDef] is an Arachneid—this caste of Arachne is the backbone of the nest. While obeying the command of the Queen species, it also commands the auxiliary insects under its command. They have shouldered different missions from the beginning of their birth, and have served the insect swarm wholeheartedly in their short lifespans.</Arachnae_Node_BS_Child_1.description>
  <Arachnae_MimicNematode_BS_Child_1.description>[PAWN_nameDef] is an Arachne parasitoid - they are not bugs in the conventional sense. These parasites parasitize and control the bodies of intelligent creatures.</Arachnae_MimicNematode_BS_Child_1.description>
  <Arachnae_MimicNematode_BS_Adult_1.description>[PAWN_nameDef] is an Arachne quasi-thread. Being produced as a body that was parasitized and controlled by Arachne's parasitic species, she had no independent consciousness of her own, and could not survive independently from the parasitism of the parasitic species.</Arachnae_MimicNematode_BS_Adult_1.description>
  <Arachnae_Node_BS_Adult_Myrmecocystus.description>[PAWN_nameDef] is an Arachne honeypot breeder. The selective expression of genes allowed her to grow a swollen stomach pouch and complex mouthparts, which allowed her to devour unprocessed corpses and various omnivores or further decompose them, and convert them into Arachne nectar through her digestive organs for other Zerg species to eat. \n\n[PAWN_nameDef] is not an opponent worth taking seriously in battle. Her combat skills are very clumsy, and her fragile and bulky nature also determines that she can hardly dodge any attack.</Arachnae_Node_BS_Adult_Myrmecocystus.description>
  <Arachnae_Node_BS_Adult_ShieldHead.description>[PAWN_nameDef] is an Arachne shield-headed worm. Shieldheads are a type of bulky Arachne zerg. They have thick, often overgrown carapace. In addition to producing chitin, they also have auxiliary limbs connected to armed organs. They can rely on the armed organs of the swarm and their own innate armor to assume the task of defending the insect nest.</Arachnae_Node_BS_Adult_ShieldHead.description>
  <Arachnae_Node_BS_Adult_WeaponSmith.description>[PAWN_nameDef] is an Arachne craft breeder. It can produce hatching cocoons specially used to hatch Arachne's armed organs to strengthen the combat effectiveness of the insect nest. \n\nAlthough [PAWN_nameDef] can pick up weapons, she is very afraid of any harm and tries to avoid direct exposure to attacks.</Arachnae_Node_BS_Adult_WeaponSmith.description>
  <Arachnae_Node_BS_Adult_Fighter.description>[PAWN_nameDef] is an Arachne warrior worm. It can hunt and carry. It is good at manipulating all worm nest weapons. It is a difficult opponent whether it is melee or long-range. Although the auxiliary worm cannot be hatched under normal conditions, it can launch the Arachne acid bite seeds into the enemy's face like a cannonball, exchanging the limited lifespan of the auxiliary worm for the enemy's long-range misfire.</Arachnae_Node_BS_Adult_Fighter.description>
  <Arachnae_Node_BS_Adult_Smokepop.description>[PAWN_nameDef] is an Arachne Mist Overlord. It is a rare large insect that can be equipped with large armed organs. She has a giant carapace that scares away other invaders, which is difficult to penetrate with conventional hand-held weapons; and she also has a huge dense fog chamber that can spray white sticky substances and white smoke that hinder combustion into a large area through multiple biological nozzles to cover the insect swarms from attacking enemy turret positions.</Arachnae_Node_BS_Adult_Smokepop.description>
  <Arachnae_Node_BS_Adult_Skyraider.description>[PAWN_nameDef] is an Arachne sky-breeding insect. As the elite of the Arachne sky-breeding insects, the sky-breeding insect has evolved powerful flying abilities and is the undisputed aerial overlord in the lair.</Arachnae_Node_BS_Adult_Skyraider.description>
  <Arachnae_Node_BS_Adult_Facehugger.description>[PAWN_nameDef] is an Arachne species. [PAWN_nameDef] takes over the victim's body by extending its unique neural link tube into the victim's body. When taking over, skill proficiency is taken as the higher of the protozoan and the victim, but any skill proficiencies gained during the parasite are not carried over when the protozoan leaves the victim.</Arachnae_Node_BS_Adult_Facehugger.description>
  <Arachnae_Node_BS_Adult_NeuroSwarm.description>[PAWN_nameDef] is an Arachneweaver worm. Although the Weaver Species are supervised by the Queen Species, they still possess powerful advanced intelligence and self-will. The Weaver Species can build a highly interconnected neural network to perform complex research and calculations. The Weaver Species cannot perceive the external environment when performing calculations, so they are important protection targets for the insect swarm.</Arachnae_Node_BS_Adult_NeuroSwarm.description>
  <Arachnae_Node_BS_Adult_Praetorian.description>[PAWN_nameDef] is an Arachne Praetorian Overlord. They are elite soldiers under the Queen, tasked with carrying out the will of the Queen's species. They can skillfully use long-range armed organs to harvest enemies gracefully, and hatch a large number of acid-eating auxiliary insects to build a defense line.</Arachnae_Node_BS_Adult_Praetorian.description>
</LanguageData>
