<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <ArachnaeNode_Race_Myrmecocystus.label>Arachne honeypot species</ArachnaeNode_Race_Myrmecocystus.label>
  <ArachnaeNode_Race_Myrmecocystus.description>One of the large Arachne worms, a large zerg with a wide range of diets. It can swallow many unprocessed creatures and break them down into Arachne nectar to nourish the worm colony. When other bugs in the swarm are hungry, they will feed them mouth-to-mouth, and if the honey pot is overflowing, they will expel the honey to create resources for nest construction. \n\nShe can carry, cook and plant, but her combat skills are very poor.</ArachnaeNode_Race_Myrmecocystus.description>
  <ArachnaeNode_Race_Myrmecocystus.comps.CompProperties_NodeSwarmLifetime.labelOverride>life</ArachnaeNode_Race_Myrmecocystus.comps.CompProperties_NodeSwarmLifetime.labelOverride>
  <ArachnaeNode_Race_Myrmecocystus.comps.CompProperties_NodeSwarmLifetime.tooltipOverride>The lives of Arachne's worms run like fine clockwork.</ArachnaeNode_Race_Myrmecocystus.comps.CompProperties_NodeSwarmLifetime.tooltipOverride>
  <ArachnaeNode_Race_ShieldHead.label>Arachne shield-headed species</ArachnaeNode_Race_ShieldHead.label>
  <ArachnaeNode_Race_ShieldHead.description>One of the Arachneid bugs, it has an overgrown carapace that covers its head and legs, and can periodically peel off chitin for use in the insect nest. \n\nShe can carry out transportation, mining and construction work. Her combat skills are mediocre, but she has good defense.</ArachnaeNode_Race_ShieldHead.description>
  <ArachnaeNode_Race_ShieldHead.comps.CompProperties_NodeSwarmLifetime.labelOverride>life</ArachnaeNode_Race_ShieldHead.comps.CompProperties_NodeSwarmLifetime.labelOverride>
  <ArachnaeNode_Race_ShieldHead.comps.CompProperties_NodeSwarmLifetime.tooltipOverride>The lives of Arachne's worms run like fine clockwork.</ArachnaeNode_Race_ShieldHead.comps.CompProperties_NodeSwarmLifetime.tooltipOverride>
  <ArachnaeNode_Race_WeaponSmith.label>Arachne Craft Type</ArachnaeNode_Race_WeaponSmith.label>
  <ArachnaeNode_Race_WeaponSmith.description>One of the Arachnedo insects, it is mainly responsible for the maintenance of the nest and using its dexterous limbs to handle some delicate work for the insect swarm. \n\nShe can carry out transportation, manual and artistic work. Her combat skills are mediocre, but she is extremely fragile.</ArachnaeNode_Race_WeaponSmith.description>
  <ArachnaeNode_Race_WeaponSmith.comps.CompProperties_NodeSwarmLifetime.labelOverride>life</ArachnaeNode_Race_WeaponSmith.comps.CompProperties_NodeSwarmLifetime.labelOverride>
  <ArachnaeNode_Race_WeaponSmith.comps.CompProperties_NodeSwarmLifetime.tooltipOverride>The lives of Arachne's worms run like fine clockwork.</ArachnaeNode_Race_WeaponSmith.comps.CompProperties_NodeSwarmLifetime.tooltipOverride>
  <ArachnaeNode_Race_Fighter.label>Arachne warrior race</ArachnaeNode_Race_Fighter.label>
  <ArachnaeNode_Race_Fighter.description>Arachne, one of the true warriors in the lair, possesses powerful plasticity genes and will gain more abilities as technology is unlocked. \n\nShe can carry, hunt, and tame animals. Her combat skills are outstanding and she moves quickly. \n\nAs a Superintendent, she can breed and supervise several Arachne Acid Seed-eating Auxiliary Insects, small but extremely tough combat-type Auxiliary Insects. In addition to absorbing artillery fire, she can also use the acidic front jaws to bite people in close combat.</ArachnaeNode_Race_Fighter.description>
  <ArachnaeNode_Race_Fighter.comps.CompProperties_NodeSwarmLifetime.labelOverride>life</ArachnaeNode_Race_Fighter.comps.CompProperties_NodeSwarmLifetime.labelOverride>
  <ArachnaeNode_Race_Fighter.comps.CompProperties_NodeSwarmLifetime.tooltipOverride>The lives of Arachne's worms run like fine clockwork.</ArachnaeNode_Race_Fighter.comps.CompProperties_NodeSwarmLifetime.tooltipOverride>
  <ArachnaeNode_Race_Fighter.tools.0.label>giant scythe</ArachnaeNode_Race_Fighter.tools.0.label>
  <ArachnaeNode_Race_Facehugger.label>Arachne species</ArachnaeNode_Race_Facehugger.label>
  <ArachnaeNode_Race_Facehugger.description>One of the Arachnidrids, a special worm in a highly undifferentiated state that can control the victim's body through unique neural link tubes and release psychic signals to make those around him ignore its existence. However, she is too fragile to be able to do any work before completing her parasitism. \n\nShe can perform all non-research tasks, and her combat skills are approximately none. \n\nUnlike ordinary Arachne zerg, its highly undifferentiated body determines that it cannot breed any auxiliary insects.</ArachnaeNode_Race_Facehugger.description>
  <ArachnaeNode_Race_Smokepop.label>Arachne Mist Seed</ArachnaeNode_Race_Smokepop.label>
  <ArachnaeNode_Race_Smokepop.description>One of Arachne's large worms, a large zerg with a thick carapace. It has the ability to spray pheromones over a wide range to summon swarms of auxiliary worms. Although it moves slowly, it is as hard to shake as an armored vehicle in battle. \n\nShe can carry out transportation work, has good combat skills, and has strong defense and damage tolerance.</ArachnaeNode_Race_Smokepop.description>
  <ArachnaeNode_Race_Smokepop.comps.CompProperties_NodeSwarmLifetime.labelOverride>life</ArachnaeNode_Race_Smokepop.comps.CompProperties_NodeSwarmLifetime.labelOverride>
  <ArachnaeNode_Race_Smokepop.comps.CompProperties_NodeSwarmLifetime.tooltipOverride>The lives of Arachne's worms run like fine clockwork.</ArachnaeNode_Race_Smokepop.comps.CompProperties_NodeSwarmLifetime.tooltipOverride>
  <ArachnaeNode_Race_Skyraider.label>Arachne Sky Seed</ArachnaeNode_Race_Skyraider.label>
  <ArachnaeNode_Race_Skyraider.description>Arachne is one of the large Overlords, the elite among all the Overlords. It is huge and possesses the proud flying ability. It is the undisputed aerial overlord in the lair. \n\nShe can carry out transportation work, has good combat skills, and is very flexible when moving on the battlefield.</ArachnaeNode_Race_Skyraider.description>
  <ArachnaeNode_Race_Skyraider.comps.CompProperties_NodeSwarmLifetime.labelOverride>life</ArachnaeNode_Race_Skyraider.comps.CompProperties_NodeSwarmLifetime.labelOverride>
  <ArachnaeNode_Race_Skyraider.comps.CompProperties_NodeSwarmLifetime.tooltipOverride>The lives of Arachne's worms run like fine clockwork.</ArachnaeNode_Race_Skyraider.comps.CompProperties_NodeSwarmLifetime.tooltipOverride>
  <ArachnaeNode_Race_NeuroSwarm.label>Arachne weaving species</ArachnaeNode_Race_NeuroSwarm.label>
  <ArachnaeNode_Race_NeuroSwarm.description>One of the Arachne worms, it is the most special zerg species in the Arachne swarm. Although the worms are supervised by the Queen species, they still have strong advanced intelligence and self-will. The worms can build a highly interconnected neural network to carry out complex research and calculations. The worms cannot sense the external environment when performing calculations, so they are important protection targets of the swarm.</ArachnaeNode_Race_NeuroSwarm.description>
  <ArachnaeNode_Race_Praetorian.label>Arachne Guards</ArachnaeNode_Race_Praetorian.label>
  <ArachnaeNode_Race_Praetorian.description>Arachne, one of the insects, is an elite soldier carefully selected and cultivated by the Queen's species, and is also the mouthpiece of the Queen's species. Not only do they have social skills that are rare in the insect hive, but they are smaller than regular large insectoids but can be equipped with large weapons. They can command nearby insectoids and are flexible enough to deal with all situations on the battlefield. \n\nShe can carry out transportation, socializing and artistic work. Her combat skills are very outstanding, and her shooting skills are even better. \n\nAs a supervisor insect, she can hatch a large number of Arachne acid seed-eating auxiliary insects at one time to form a difficult front.</ArachnaeNode_Race_Praetorian.description>
  <ArachnaeNode_Race_Praetorian.comps.CompProperties_NodeSwarmLifetime.labelOverride>life</ArachnaeNode_Race_Praetorian.comps.CompProperties_NodeSwarmLifetime.labelOverride>
  <ArachnaeNode_Race_Praetorian.comps.CompProperties_NodeSwarmLifetime.tooltipOverride>The lives of Arachne's worms run like fine clockwork.</ArachnaeNode_Race_Praetorian.comps.CompProperties_NodeSwarmLifetime.tooltipOverride>
  <ArachnaeNode_Race_MimicNematode.label>Arachne</ArachnaeNode_Race_MimicNematode.label>
  <ArachnaeNode_Race_MimicNematode.description>Strictly speaking, the parasitic species belong to the Arachne auxiliary worm, which usually takes over the victim's body in a parasitic manner. However, under special circumstances, the Arachne worm will also actively cultivate the body of the parasitic species to help the insect nest. \n\nDue to genetic defects, the pseudonym actually still controls an unconscious body in a parasitic manner, which makes the pseudonym only rely on instinct to act and cannot link to the hive mind.</ArachnaeNode_Race_MimicNematode.description>
</LanguageData>
