<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
<ARA_Titan_Base_Technology.label>Titan antenna specialization</ARA_Titan_Base_Technology.label>
<ARA_Titan_Base_Technology.description>&lt;color=#915A30&gt;&lt;i&gt;Arachne Insect Group - Titan Antenna\nTitan Antenna is the main force of the Arachne Insect Group.It is composed of the most robust and adaptable species among the insect groups, and is responsible for maintaining the front lines on the battlefield.This family of insect groups has a good balance between offense and defense. ,He specializes in tactics that defeat opponents head-on.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/color&gt;\n\nUnlocks the research path for the Arachne Insect Swarm Titan Antenna.\n\nThis technology cannot be researched voluntarily. It is unlocked by the Arachne Empress at the start of the game.</ARA_Titan_Base_Technology.description>
<ARA_Technology_8SLA.label>Node SLA-8 "Beast of Violence"</ARA_Technology_8SLA.label>
<ARA_Technology_8SLA.description>&lt;color=#915A30&gt;&lt;i&gt;Arachne Insect Group - Titan Antenna\nTitan Antenna is the main force of the Arachne Insect Group.It is composed of the most robust and adaptable species among the insect groups, and is responsible for maintaining the front line on the battlefield.This family of insect groups has a good balance between offense and defense. , and specializes in tactics that defeat opponents head-on.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/color&gt;\n\nAllows the hatching of new beast insects by the Empress type - the Slaughter Type.\n\nAll technologies that require the Titan antenna blueprints of the Arachne insect group can only be researched through genetic experiment eggs.</ARA_Technology_8SLA.description>
<ARA_Technology_7ACD_T.label>Node ACD-7 "Solid strong acid"</ARA_Technology_7ACD_T.label>
<ARA_Technology_7ACD_T.description>&lt;color=#915A30&gt;&lt;i&gt;Arachne Insect Group - Titan Antenna\nTitan Antenna is the main force of Arachne Insect Group, and is composed of the most robust and adaptable species among the insect groups, and is responsible for maintaining the front line on the battlefield.This family of insect groups has a well-balanced offense and defense, and is good at tactics that defeat the opponent head-on. .&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/color&gt;\n\nBy allowing the honeycan species to undergo certain evolutions and sacrificing their ability to hatch worms, we obtain a strong acid that dissolves prisoners and captives and quickly obtains nectar.\n\nAll technologies that require the Titan Antenna Blueprint of the Arachnida swarm can only be studied through genetic experiment eggs.</ARA_Technology_7ACD_T.description>
<ARA_Technology_3LGN_T.label>Node LGN-3 "Legion Power"</ARA_Technology_3LGN_T.label>
<ARA_Technology_3LGN_T.description>&lt;color=#915A30&gt;&lt;i&gt;Arachne Insect Group - Titan Antenna\nTitan Antenna is the main force of Arachne Insect Group, and is composed of the most robust and adaptable species among the insect groups, and is responsible for maintaining the front lines on the battlefield.This family of insect groups has a well-balanced offense and defense, and is good at tactics that defeat the opponent head-on. .&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/color&gt;\n\nForbidden species undergo directional evolution, losing the ability to hatch worms, but gaining stronger melee combat abilities, long-range attack abilities, defensive abilities, and various physical techniques.\n\nAll technologies that require the Arachne Bug Titan Antenna Blueprint can only be researched through genetic experiment eggs.</ARA_Technology_3LGN_T.description>
<ARA_Technology_6LOD_T.label>Node LOD-6 "Lord of the Nest"</ARA_Technology_6LOD_T.label>
<ARA_Technology_6LOD_T.description>&lt;color=#915A30&gt;&lt;i&gt;Arachne Insect Group - Titan Antenna\nTitan Antenna is the main force of the Arachne Insect Group, and is made up of the most robust and adaptable species among the insect groups, and is responsible for maintaining the front line on the battlefield.This family of insect groups has a well-balanced offense and defense, and is good at tactics that defeat the opponent head-on.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/c olor&gt;\n\nThe Aerial Species undergo directional evolution, sacrificing their high speed and high-altitude maneuverability in exchange for the ability to project large numbers of Celestial Species at their enemies. These flying insects are extremely fast and extremely troublesome in close combat.\n\nAll technologies that require the Titan Antenna Blueprint of the Arachne Bugs can only be researched through Genetic Experimental Eggs.</ARA_Technology_6LOD_T.description>
<ARA_Technology_7EVO_T.label>Node EVO-7 "Carapace Spines"</ARA_Technology_7EVO_T.label>
<ARA_Technology_7EVO_T.description>&lt;color=#915A30&gt;&lt;i&gt;Arachne Insect Group - Titan Antenna\nTitan Antenna is the main force of the Arachne Insect Group.It is composed of the most robust and adaptable species among the insect groups, and is responsible for maintaining the front line on the battlefield.This family of insect groups has a well-balanced offense and defense, and uses tactics to defeat the opponent head-on. It specializes in.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/color&gt;\n\nAllows the implementation of a new Arachne evolution surgery, in which the spinous canals implanted with Arachne bugs will automatically attack nearby enemies.\n\nAll techniques that require Arachne bug Titan antenna blueprints can only be researched through genetic experiment eggs.</ARA_Technology_7EVO_T.description>
<ARA_Technology_1STG_T.label>Node STG-1 "Release Cavity"</ARA_Technology_1STG_T.label>
<ARA_Technology_1STG_T.description>&lt;color=#915A30&gt;&lt;i&gt;Arachne Insects - Titan Antenna\nThe Titan Antenna is the main force of the Arachne Insects, consisting of the most robust and adaptable species of insects, and is responsible for maintaining the front line on the battlefield. This family of insects has a well-balanced attack and defense, and specializes in tactics that defeat opponents head-on.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/color&gt;\n\nYou will be able to hatch new weapons from Arachne cocoons.</ARA_Technology_1STG_T.description>
<ARA_Technology_3XPV_T.label>Node XPV-3 "梭镖"</ARA_Technology_3XPV_T.label>
<ARA_Technology_3XPV_T.description>&lt;color=#915A30&gt;&lt;i&gt;Arachne Insects - Titan Antenna\nThe Titan Antenna is the main force of the Arachne Insects, consisting of the most robust and adaptable species of insects, and is responsible for maintaining the front line on the battlefield. This family of insects has a well-balanced attack and defense, and specializes in tactics that defeat opponents head-on.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/color&gt;\n\nYou will be able to hatch new weapons from Arachne cocoons.</ARA_Technology_3XPV_T.description>
</LanguageData>
