<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
<ARA_Incubator_1_Flaw_Hediffs.label>endocrine imbalance</ARA_Incubator_1_Flaw_Hediffs.label>
<ARA_Incubator_1_Flaw_Hediffs.description>Due to the rapid hatching, the endocrine system of this Arachnid insect undergoes abnormal development, and various hormones in the body are maintained at low levels for a long time.\n\nDue to the poor hatching quality, this Arachnid insect has acquired disadvantageous mutations.</ARA_Incubator_1_Flaw_Hediffs.description>
<ARA_Incubator_2_Flaw_Hediffs.label>Exoskeleton defect</ARA_Incubator_2_Flaw_Hediffs.label>
<ARA_Incubator_2_Flaw_Hediffs.description>Due to rapid hatching, this Arachne insect is unable to form a complete exoskeleton, making it extremely fragile.\n\nDue to poor hatching quality, this Arachne insect has acquired disadvantageous mutations.</ARA_Incubator_2_Flaw_Hediffs.description>
<ARA_Incubator_3_Flaw_Hediffs.label>ataxia</ARA_Incubator_3_Flaw_Hediffs.label>
<ARA_Incubator_3_Flaw_Hediffs.description>Due to rapid hatching, this Arachne insect's nervous system has been severely slowed down. Not only is it unable to remember things, but even daily tasks are impaired.\n\nDue to poor hatching quality, this Arachne insect has acquired an unfavorable mutation.</ARA_Incubator_3_Flaw_Hediffs.description>
<ARA_Incubator_4_Flaw_Hediffs.label>severe visual impairment</ARA_Incubator_4_Flaw_Hediffs.label>
<ARA_Incubator_4_Flaw_Hediffs.description>Due to rapid hatching, the external sense organs of this Arachne insect are not fully developed.\n\nDue to poor hatching quality, this Arachne insect has acquired disadvantageous mutations.</ARA_Incubator_4_Flaw_Hediffs.description>
<ARA_Incubator_1_Reward_Hediffs.label>dense carapace</ARA_Incubator_1_Reward_Hediffs.label>
<ARA_Incubator_1_Reward_Hediffs.description>The shell of this Arachne Insect is denser than that of normal insects, and as a result, the shell has acquired additional protection.\n\nDue to good hatching quality, the Arachne Insect has acquired this advantageous mutation.</ARA_Incubator_1_Reward_Hediffs.description>
<ARA_Incubator_2_Reward_Hediffs.label>Undershell refractory fat</ARA_Incubator_2_Reward_Hediffs.label>
<ARA_Incubator_2_Reward_Hediffs.description>The subcutaneous fat of this Arachne insect has acquired fire resistance due to an advantageous mutation. When the insect is burned by flames, the fire-resistant fat layer ruptures and extinguishes the fire that spreads to its body.\n\nDue to good hatching quality, the Arachne insect has acquired this advantageous mutation.</ARA_Incubator_2_Reward_Hediffs.description>
<ARA_Incubator_3_Reward_Hediffs.label>behavioral hormones</ARA_Incubator_3_Reward_Hediffs.label>
<ARA_Incubator_3_Reward_Hediffs.description>The glandular body of this Arachne insect is highly abnormal and constantly secretes hormones to keep it in a state of excitement.The effect is also transmitted to the linked weapon organs.\n\nDue to good hatching quality, the Arachne insect has acquired this advantageous mutation.</ARA_Incubator_3_Reward_Hediffs.description>
<ARA_Incubator_4_Reward_Hediffs.label>high resting visual acuity</ARA_Incubator_4_Reward_Hediffs.label>
<ARA_Incubator_4_Reward_Hediffs.description>Due to an advantageous mutation, this Arachne Insect has acquired a high level of static vision that is different from other insect families. This compensates for its weak eyesight and greatly improves its ease of use when shooting.\n\nBecause of its good hatching quality, the Arachne Insect has acquired this advantageous mutation.</ARA_Incubator_4_Reward_Hediffs.description>
<ARA_Incubator_5_Reward_Hediffs.label>strong muscles</ARA_Incubator_5_Reward_Hediffs.label>
<ARA_Incubator_5_Reward_Hediffs.description>This Arachne insect is surprisingly muscular and in a manner of overfed.\n\nDue to good hatching quality, the Arachne insect has acquired this advantageous mutation.</ARA_Incubator_5_Reward_Hediffs.description>
<ARA_Incubator_6_Reward_Hediffs.label>central strengthening</ARA_Incubator_6_Reward_Hediffs.label>
<ARA_Incubator_6_Reward_Hediffs.description>The neural responses of this Arachne insect far exceed those of other insect families. The enhanced reflexes make its actions agile and deadly.\n\nDue to good hatching quality, the Arachne insect has acquired this advantageous mutation.</ARA_Incubator_6_Reward_Hediffs.description>
<ARA_Incubator_7_Reward_Hediffs.label>plastic memory</ARA_Incubator_7_Reward_Hediffs.label>
<ARA_Incubator_7_Reward_Hediffs.description>The memory structure of this Arachne insect is more complex, allowing it to quickly absorb new knowledge and experience.\n\nDue to good hatching quality, the Arachne insect has acquired this advantageous mutation.</ARA_Incubator_7_Reward_Hediffs.description>
<ARA_Incubator_8_Reward_Hediffs.label>clotting factor</ARA_Incubator_8_Reward_Hediffs.label>
<ARA_Incubator_8_Reward_Hediffs.description>The blood clotting system of this Arachne worm has been made more efficient. Several special clotting factors not present in other worms have significantly reduced the rate of bleeding.\n\nDue to good hatching quality, the Arachne worm has acquired this advantageous mutation.</ARA_Incubator_8_Reward_Hediffs.description>
<ARA_Incubator_5_Flaw_Hediffs.label>muscle atrophy</ARA_Incubator_5_Flaw_Hediffs.label>
<ARA_Incubator_5_Flaw_Hediffs.description>Due to rapid hatching, the musculature of this Arachne insect is not fully developed and its strength is far below that of a normal individual.\n\nDue to poor hatching quality, the Arachne insect has acquired this disadvantageous mutation.</ARA_Incubator_5_Flaw_Hediffs.description>
<ARA_Incubator_6_Flaw_Hediffs.label>coagulopathy</ARA_Incubator_6_Flaw_Hediffs.label>
<ARA_Incubator_6_Flaw_Hediffs.description>Due to rapid hatching, the blood clotting mechanism of this Arachne insect is abnormal, causing it to bleed profusely when injured.\n\nDue to poor hatching quality, the Arachne insect has acquired this disadvantageous mutation.</ARA_Incubator_6_Flaw_Hediffs.description>
<ARA_Incubator_7_Flaw_Hediffs.label>osteoporosis</ARA_Incubator_7_Flaw_Hediffs.label>
<ARA_Incubator_7_Flaw_Hediffs.description>Due to rapid hatching, the endoskeleton of this Arachne insect is unusually fragile and susceptible to fatal injuries.\n\nDue to poor hatching quality, the Arachne insect has acquired this disadvantageous mutation.</ARA_Incubator_7_Flaw_Hediffs.description>
<ARA_Incubator_8_Flaw_Hediffs.label>immunodeficiency</ARA_Incubator_8_Flaw_Hediffs.label>
<ARA_Incubator_8_Flaw_Hediffs.description>Due to rapid hatching, the immune system of this Arachnid insect is immature and its resistance to disease is extremely low.\n\nDue to poor hatching quality, the Arachnid insect has acquired this disadvantageous mutation.</ARA_Incubator_8_Flaw_Hediffs.description>
<ARA_Incubator_Elite_Regeneration.label>Ultra-dense shell</ARA_Incubator_Elite_Regeneration.label>
<ARA_Incubator_Elite_Regeneration.description>The shell density of this Arachne insect is much higher than that of a normal individual, and it is almost indestructible and has excellent heat resistance.\n\nDue to extremely high hatching quality, the Arachne insect has acquired this rare mutation.</ARA_Incubator_Elite_Regeneration.description>
<ARA_Incubator_Elite_AdaptiveArmor.label>super hormone</ARA_Incubator_Elite_AdaptiveArmor.label>
<ARA_Incubator_Elite_AdaptiveArmor.description>The glands of this Arachne insect are abnormally developed, and they continuously secrete high concentrations of hormones, making them extremely excited. Their attack speed is astonishing.\n\nDue to extremely high hatching quality, the Arachne insect has acquired this rare mutation.</ARA_Incubator_Elite_AdaptiveArmor.description>
<ARA_Incubator_Elite_BerserkGlands.label>full muscle</ARA_Incubator_Elite_BerserkGlands.label>
<ARA_Incubator_Elite_BerserkGlands.description>This Arachne Insect's musculature is perfectly developed, and its strength far exceeds that of its kin.The power of its melee attacks is tremendous, and its carrying capacity has been greatly improved.\n\nDue to extremely high hatching quality, the Arachne Insect has acquired this rare mutation.</ARA_Incubator_Elite_BerserkGlands.description>
<ARA_Incubator_Elite_PsychicResonance.label>ultimate consciousness</ARA_Incubator_Elite_PsychicResonance.label>
<ARA_Incubator_Elite_PsychicResonance.description>The Arachne insect's nervous system is perfectly developed, and all sensory abilities, including consciousness, vision, and hearing, far exceed those of its congeners.\n\nDue to extremely high hatching quality, the Arachne insect has acquired this rare mutation.</ARA_Incubator_Elite_PsychicResonance.description>
</LanguageData>
