<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
<ARA_GuardianPsyField.label>Origen Psychic Field</ARA_GuardianPsyField.label>
<ARA_GuardianPsyField.description>A powerful psychic defense field that automatically intercepts hostile flying objects that enter its range of action.The total amount of the shield depends on psychic sensitivity and is difficult to penetrate, but psychic entropy is accumulated each time it is intercepted.</ARA_GuardianPsyField.description>
<ARA_Psi_Master.label>psychic master</ARA_Psi_Master.label>
<ARA_Psi_Master.description>The Arachne Orioles are the psychic masters of the colony. They are adept at using psychic abilities, and can use them not only for their own flight, but also as a conduit to protect nearby friendly units and fire energy attacks at enemies.</ARA_Psi_Master.description>
<ARA_Psi_Conductor.label>psychic conductor</ARA_Psi_Conductor.label>
<ARA_Psi_Conductor.description>The arachne Oria species uses this colonist as a conductor for its own powerful psychic energy. The Oria species controls the colonist's psychic ability to perform automatic attacks on enemies, making the colonist more difficult to defeat—at the cost of putting the colonist into a short period of psychoshock.</ARA_Psi_Conductor.description>
<ARA_Praetorian_Commander_Hediff.label>command node</ARA_Praetorian_Commander_Hediff.label>
<ARA_Praetorian_Commander_Hediff.description>The Arachne Forbidden Species commands the insect tribe troops around them, but their combat power is reduced because they have dispersed their consciousness to create a secondary hive mind network.</ARA_Praetorian_Commander_Hediff.description>
<ARA_Praetorian_Command_Hediff.label>hive command</ARA_Praetorian_Command_Hediff.label>
<ARA_Praetorian_Command_Hediff.description>Nearby Arachne Forbidden Species serve as battlefield commanders. The Arachne Bug Tribes under their command are connected by a secondary hive mind network, enhancing their overall combat capabilities.</ARA_Praetorian_Command_Hediff.description>
<ARA_SwarmSpell_Overdrive.label>psychic nerve bundle overload</ARA_SwarmSpell_Overdrive.label>
<ARA_SwarmSpell_Overdrive.description>An Arachne spirit sucker's nerve bundles enter a state of overload with repeated spells; this condition continually puts pressure on the spirit sucker's nervous system until it is completely burnt out.\n\nThis condition cannot be relieved on its own, and the spirit sucker has no choice but to divert this high load to other individuals. For individuals with a psy-link, this diversion is not fatal, but for individuals without a psy-link, this is not necessarily the case.</ARA_SwarmSpell_Overdrive.description>
</LanguageData>
