<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <ARA_HiveMindMaster.label>Queen Arachne</ARA_HiveMindMaster.label>
  <ARA_HiveMindMaster.description>The Arachne Queen species is the central node of the insect swarm's consciousness, serving as the mastermind to govern the entire Arachne insect swarm. There are a large number of undifferentiated repair cells in its body, which can heal all wounds on its own at a speed that ordinary people cannot imagine.</ARA_HiveMindMaster.description>
  <ARA_HiveMindMaster.stages.0.label>Connect to {0} Swarm Workers</ARA_HiveMindMaster.stages.0.label>
  <ARA_HiveMindDrone.label>Arachneid</ARA_HiveMindDrone.label>
  <ARA_HiveMindDrone.description>The Arachneid is linked to the Arachne Empress species through the mind. If the queen dies, the insect will also cease life activities.</ARA_HiveMindDrone.description>
  <ARA_HiveMindDrone.comps.HediffCompProperties_MessageAfterTicks.letterLabel>{0_labelShort} is born</ARA_HiveMindDrone.comps.HediffCompProperties_MessageAfterTicks.letterLabel>
  <ARA_HiveMindDrone.comps.HediffCompProperties_MessageAfterTicks.letterText>A new Arachneid {0_labelShort} has emerged from its cocoon! She is wandering around, waiting for instructions from the Queen Species - to use the Arachne Queen Species' pheromone marking skill to complete the link, or to wait for it to establish the link on its own.</ARA_HiveMindDrone.comps.HediffCompProperties_MessageAfterTicks.letterText>
  <ARA_NonPlayer_HiveMindDroneHediff.label>feral swarm</ARA_NonPlayer_HiveMindDroneHediff.label>
  <ARA_NonPlayer_HiveMindDroneHediff.description>Overlords disconnected from the hive mind of the Arachne Swarm will only act like beasts - the Queenseed can take over them again.</ARA_NonPlayer_HiveMindDroneHediff.description>
  <ARA_HiveMindWorker.label>Arachne</ARA_HiveMindWorker.label>
  <ARA_HiveMindWorker.description>The Arachneid is linked to the Arachneid species through the mind. If the worm dies, the auxiliary worm will also stop life activities.</ARA_HiveMindWorker.description>
  <ARA_HiveMindBeast.label>Arachne</ARA_HiveMindBeast.label>
  <ARA_HiveMindBeast.description>The Arachne Beast Bug is a more primitive life form than other Arachne Bugs. It has a simple mind and well-developed limbs, but it does not follow the pyramid thinking of the hive. Any Overlord and Queen in the hive can command them.</ARA_HiveMindBeast.description>
  <ARA_HiveStrength_Pluse.label>Insect swarm alien blood</ARA_HiveStrength_Pluse.label>
  <ARA_HiveStrength_Pluse.description>The repair cells of this Arachne Zerg are beyond common sense, and it is almost impossible to kill it no matter how serious the injury is. In addition, this powerful cell also confers protection against acid corrosion and arachnid acid.</ARA_HiveStrength_Pluse.description>
  <ARA_HiveStrength.label>Swarm Vitality</ARA_HiveStrength.label>
  <ARA_HiveStrength.description>The repair cells of this Arachne Zerg are unique. They can automatically heal injuries at a very fast speed and even regenerate some lost organs. In addition, this powerful cell also confers protection against acid corrosion and arachnid acid.</ARA_HiveStrength.description>
  <ARA_HiveStrength_Low.label>The swarm is strong</ARA_HiveStrength_Low.label>
  <ARA_HiveStrength_Low.description>The Arachne Zerg's ability to repair injuries is quite powerful, and they can quickly recover from various fatal blows. In addition, this powerful cell also confers protection against acid corrosion and arachnid acid.</ARA_HiveStrength_Low.description>
  <ARA_LifespanHediff.label>life record</ARA_LifespanHediff.label>
  <ARA_LifespanHediff.description>The Arachne Zerg's hediff records lifespan. Normally you shouldn't see this.</ARA_LifespanHediff.description>
  <ARA_TemperatureRegulation.label>cold blooded animals</ARA_TemperatureRegulation.label>
  <ARA_TemperatureRegulation.description>The Arachne Zerg are cold-blooded animals, which means they are more sensitive to changes in external temperature - they will become agile and deadly under suitable temperatures, but they will be unable to move under uncomfortable temperatures. \n\nThis type of Arachne Zerg can accept activities at temperatures of 6~36°C, and will gain additional awareness bonuses when the temperature approaches 21°C.</ARA_TemperatureRegulation.description>
  <ARA_TemperatureRegulation.stages.0.label>discomfort</ARA_TemperatureRegulation.stages.0.label>
  <ARA_TemperatureRegulation.stages.1.label>adapt</ARA_TemperatureRegulation.stages.1.label>
  <ARA_TemperatureRegulation.stages.2.label>Comfortable</ARA_TemperatureRegulation.stages.2.label>
  <ARA_RaceBaseSwarmProduceSwitchHediff.label>breeding inhibition</ARA_RaceBaseSwarmProduceSwitchHediff.label>
  <ARA_RaceBaseSwarmProduceSwitchHediff.description>This Arachnidok has been prohibited from breeding auxiliaries by the hive mind.</ARA_RaceBaseSwarmProduceSwitchHediff.description>
  <ARA_Hive_Cannot_Speak.label>Can't speak</ARA_Hive_Cannot_Speak.label>
  <ARA_Hive_Cannot_Speak.description>Well, actually Chongchong can't speak, you should know this, right?</ARA_Hive_Cannot_Speak.description>
  <ARA_ChitinArmor.label>Carapace Armor</ARA_ChitinArmor.label>
  <ARA_ChitinArmor.description>The carapace on the Arachne Zerg can provide protection for the Arachne Zerg depending on its thickness.</ARA_ChitinArmor.description>
  <ARA_ChitinArmor.stages.0.label>Extremely thin</ARA_ChitinArmor.stages.0.label>
  <ARA_ChitinArmor.stages.1.label>Thin</ARA_ChitinArmor.stages.1.label>
  <ARA_ChitinArmor.stages.2.label>Moderate</ARA_ChitinArmor.stages.2.label>
  <ARA_ChitinArmor.stages.3.label>thicker</ARA_ChitinArmor.stages.3.label>
  <ARA_ChitinArmor.stages.4.label>thick</ARA_ChitinArmor.stages.4.label>
  <ARA_ChitinArmor.stages.5.label>Extremely thick</ARA_ChitinArmor.stages.5.label>
  <ARA_ChitinArmor.stages.6.label>solid as a rock</ARA_ChitinArmor.stages.6.label>
  <ARA_ChitinArmor.stages.7.label>indestructible</ARA_ChitinArmor.stages.7.label>
</LanguageData>
