<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <ARA_TerrainMoveSpeedHediff.label>Creep bonus: movement speed</ARA_TerrainMoveSpeedHediff.label>
  <ARA_TerrainMoveSpeedHediff.description>The fabric that this Arakid is wearing allows it to move at a higher speed on creep. The longer you stay on the creep, the stronger the effect will be, and the effect will gradually decay after leaving the creep.</ARA_TerrainMoveSpeedHediff.description>
  <ARA_TerrainMoveSpeedHediff.stages.0.label>none</ARA_TerrainMoveSpeedHediff.stages.0.label>
  <ARA_TerrainWorkSpeedHediff.label>Creep bonus: working speed</ARA_TerrainWorkSpeedHediff.label>
  <ARA_TerrainWorkSpeedHediff.description>The fabric that this Arakid is clad in allows it to work at a higher speed on creep. The longer you stay on the creep, the stronger the effect will be, and the effect will gradually decay after leaving the creep.</ARA_TerrainWorkSpeedHediff.description>
  <ARA_TerrainWorkSpeedHediff.stages.0.label>none</ARA_TerrainWorkSpeedHediff.stages.0.label>
  <ARA_TerrainCooldownHediff.label>Creep Bonus: Combat Reaction</ARA_TerrainCooldownHediff.label>
  <ARA_TerrainCooldownHediff.description>The Arakid is clad in fabric that allows it to have shorter melee and ranged cooldowns on creep. The longer you stay on the creep, the stronger the effect will be, and the effect will gradually decay after leaving the creep.</ARA_TerrainCooldownHediff.description>
  <ARA_TerrainCooldownHediff.stages.0.label>none</ARA_TerrainCooldownHediff.stages.0.label>
  <ARA_TerrainAccuracyHediff.label>Creep bonus: shooting accuracy</ARA_TerrainAccuracyHediff.label>
  <ARA_TerrainAccuracyHediff.description>The fabric that this Arakid is wearing allows it to shoot more accurately on creep. The longer you stay on the creep, the stronger the effect will be, and the effect will gradually decay after leaving the creep.</ARA_TerrainAccuracyHediff.description>
  <ARA_TerrainAccuracyHediff.stages.0.label>none</ARA_TerrainAccuracyHediff.stages.0.label>
  <ARA_TerrainCaravanSpeedHediff.label>Creep Bonus: Expedition Strengthening</ARA_TerrainCaravanSpeedHediff.label>
  <ARA_TerrainCaravanSpeedHediff.description>The Arakid is clad in fabric that allows it to gain increased caravan speed and trade capabilities on creep. The longer you stay on the creep, the stronger the effect will be, and the effect will decay at a slower rate after leaving the creep.</ARA_TerrainCaravanSpeedHediff.description>
  <ARA_TerrainCaravanSpeedHediff.stages.0.label>none</ARA_TerrainCaravanSpeedHediff.stages.0.label>
  <ARA_TerrainRestRateHediff.label>Creep bonus: Rest rate</ARA_TerrainRestRateHediff.label>
  <ARA_TerrainRestRateHediff.description>The fabric that this Arachid is wearing allows it to rest at a higher rate on creep. The longer you stay on the creep, the stronger the effect will be, and the effect will gradually decay after leaving the creep.</ARA_TerrainRestRateHediff.description>
  <ARA_TerrainRestRateHediff.stages.0.label>none</ARA_TerrainRestRateHediff.stages.0.label>
  <ARA_TerrainHealHediff.label>Creep Bonus: Healing</ARA_TerrainHealHediff.label>
  <ARA_TerrainHealHediff.description>The fabric worn by this arachnid gives it the ability to heal others.</ARA_TerrainHealHediff.description>
  <ARA_Heal_By_Nurse_Hediff.label>Swarm Cure</ARA_Heal_By_Nurse_Hediff.label>
  <ARA_Heal_By_Nurse_Hediff.description>The healing hormone of the Arachne group can cause abnormal proliferation of tissue cells to quickly complete wound healing.</ARA_Heal_By_Nurse_Hediff.description>
  <ARA_TerrainTemptHediff.label>Creep Bonus: Charm</ARA_TerrainTemptHediff.label>
  <ARA_TerrainTemptHediff.description>The fabric worn by this Arakid insect gives it the ability to distort minds and seduce others.</ARA_TerrainTemptHediff.description>
  <ARA_TerrainTerrorRoar_Hediff.label>Creep Bonus: Roar</ARA_TerrainTerrorRoar_Hediff.label>
  <ARA_TerrainTerrorRoar_Hediff.description>The fabric worn by this Arakid has given it the ability to emit a majestic roar, which can arouse fear in the hearts of enemies and force them to flee in terror.</ARA_TerrainTerrorRoar_Hediff.description>
  <ARA_Smokepop_Creeper_Hediff.label>Creep carpet laying</ARA_Smokepop_Creeper_Hediff.label>
  <ARA_Smokepop_Creeper_Hediff.description>The Arachne king insect species is laying down a carpet of bacteria, changing the nearby terrain every once in a while.</ARA_Smokepop_Creeper_Hediff.description>
</LanguageData>
