<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>

  <ARA_Queen_0_Stage.label>Evolution level - none</ARA_Queen_0_Stage.label>
  <ARA_Queen_0_Stage.description>This Arachne Queen species has just entered the chaotic edge world. Its genetic expression has not yet been understood. She also needs more experience to think about how to lead the nest forward.</ARA_Queen_0_Stage.description>
  <ARA_Queen_1_Stage.label>Evolution Level - Level 1</ARA_Queen_1_Stage.label>
  <ARA_Queen_1_Stage.description>The Arachne queen gained insights into developing her hive, and she could weave a web of genes into a more complex and powerful swarm.</ARA_Queen_1_Stage.description>
  <ARA_Queen_2_Stage.label>Evolution Level - Level 2</ARA_Queen_2_Stage.label>
  <ARA_Queen_2_Stage.description>The Arachne queen gained insights into developing her hive, and she could weave a web of genes into a more complex and powerful swarm.</ARA_Queen_2_Stage.description>
  <ARA_WeaponSmith_0_Stage.label>Evolution level - none</ARA_WeaponSmith_0_Stage.label>
  <ARA_WeaponSmith_0_Stage.description>This Arachne craft species has not yet received any enhancements and can only hatch the most common cocoons to produce some early equipment.</ARA_WeaponSmith_0_Stage.description>
  <ARA_WeaponSmith_1_Stage.label>Evolution Level - Level 1</ARA_WeaponSmith_1_Stage.label>
  <ARA_WeaponSmith_1_Stage.description>This Arachne craft has gained more powerful hatching capabilities through the Hive Mind's brilliance, and now she can breed more complex cocoons to obtain powerful equipment.</ARA_WeaponSmith_1_Stage.description>
  <ARA_WeaponSmith_2_Stage.label>Evolution Level - Level 2</ARA_WeaponSmith_2_Stage.label>
  <ARA_WeaponSmith_2_Stage.description>This Arachne craft has gained more powerful hatching capabilities through the Hive Mind's brilliance, and now she can breed more complex cocoons to obtain powerful equipment.</ARA_WeaponSmith_2_Stage.description>
  <ARA_Myrmecocystus_Production_InsectJelly.label>Produce insect honey</ARA_Myrmecocystus_Production_InsectJelly.label>
  <ARA_Myrmecocystus_Production_InsectJelly.description>This Arachne honeypot species is producing insect honey to nourish the insect colony. A honeypot species produces 15 Arachne Honey per day.</ARA_Myrmecocystus_Production_InsectJelly.description>
  <ARA_Myrmecocystus_Production_Medicine.label>Subspecies - Healing Species</ARA_Myrmecocystus_Production_Medicine.label>
  <ARA_Myrmecocystus_Production_Medicine.description>This Arachne honeypot species has been enlightened and no longer produces insect honey. Instead, it produces medicines and chemicals that are scarce in the nest, and can control parasitic parasites.</ARA_Myrmecocystus_Production_Medicine.description>
  <ARA_Myrmecocystus_Production_Fuel.label>Subspecies - deflagration species</ARA_Myrmecocystus_Production_Fuel.label>
  <ARA_Myrmecocystus_Production_Fuel.description>This Arachne honeypot species has been enchanted and no longer produces insect honey, but produces the scarce chemical fuel for the nest, and can fight enemies by spraying fire.</ARA_Myrmecocystus_Production_Fuel.description>
  <ARA_Fighter_Base.label>Hive Marine</ARA_Fighter_Base.label>
  <ARA_Fighter_Base.description>Arachne's warrior bugs can turn their bodies into their most powerful weapons. As technology is unlocked, they will gain access to a variety of skills for use.</ARA_Fighter_Base.description>
  <ARA_Fighter_Invisibility.label>Subspecies - hunter species</ARA_Fighter_Invisibility.label>
  <ARA_Fighter_Invisibility.description>The evolved warrior species has acquired special iris cells covering the whole body. These cells containing nanocrystals can refract light everywhere to achieve a permanent invisible state until they launch an attack. In addition, they have also gained more powerful close-range combat capabilities. The disadvantage is that the degradation of the compound eyes makes it difficult to shoot.</ARA_Fighter_Invisibility.description>
  <ARA_Fighter_Genestealer.label>Subspecies-Aberration</ARA_Fighter_Genestealer.label>
  <ARA_Fighter_Genestealer.description>The mutants are a mobile gene pool. They no longer have the job of licking blood among the swarms, but focus on purifying the high-quality genes of prisoners and slaves and giving them to high-quality individuals in the zerg.</ARA_Fighter_Genestealer.description>
  <ARA_Smokepop_Base.label>Living cigarette can</ARA_Smokepop_Base.label>
  <ARA_Smokepop_Base.description>The Mist Seeds are the big guys among the Arachne Zerg. They not only have thick shells, but their abdomens filled with pheromone smoke can emit gas that covers the battlefield, attracting smaller auxiliary insects to break out of the ground and launch crazy attacks on the enemy.</ARA_Smokepop_Base.description>
  <ARA_Smokepop_Production_Bacterium.label>Subspecies-breeding strain</ARA_Smokepop_Production_Bacterium.label>
  <ARA_Smokepop_Production_Bacterium.description>This Arachne Mist Species has obtained its glory, the front carapace has fallen off and it can no longer emit pheromones, in exchange for the ability to produce activated bacteria. One breeding strain produces 5 servings of activated bacteria every day.</ARA_Smokepop_Production_Bacterium.description>
  <ARA_Smokepop_Creeper.label>Subspecies-king species</ARA_Smokepop_Creeper.label>
  <ARA_Smokepop_Creeper.description>This Arachne Mist Seed has been granted Bazhao and can move around while laying down creep to transform the terrain around its lair or establish a path to invade other settlements. In addition, it also gained the ability to project fungi at enemies.</ARA_Smokepop_Creeper.description>
  <ARA_ShieldHead_Base.label>hard carapace</ARA_ShieldHead_Base.label>
  <ARA_ShieldHead_Base.description>Although the shield-headed species is smaller and does not feel as oppressive as the large Arachne Zerg, its defense is no weaker than those of the large Zerg due to the carapace covering its body. Its carapace is designed to overgrow and fall off, allowing the Zerg to use its shed carapace as a tool for nest building. A shieldhead produces 15 servings of chitin every day.</ARA_ShieldHead_Base.description>
  <ARA_ShieldHead_Protector.label>Subspecies-nest guard species</ARA_ShieldHead_Protector.label>
  <ARA_ShieldHead_Protector.description>This Arachne shield-headed creature has gained brilliance, making its combat abilities even more powerful and allowing it to attack opponents with powerful rams.</ARA_ShieldHead_Protector.description>
  <ARA_ShieldHead_HiveBuilder.label>Subspecies-constructed species</ARA_ShieldHead_HiveBuilder.label>
  <ARA_ShieldHead_HiveBuilder.description>This Arachne shield-headed species has been granted glory and has strong output and construction capabilities. A shieldhead species produces 25 servings of chitin per day.</ARA_ShieldHead_HiveBuilder.description>
  <ARA_Skyraider_Base.label>Flying behemoth</ARA_Skyraider_Base.label>
  <ARA_Skyraider_Base.description>Rulers of the sky, the Arachne Skyborn are large but agile and deadly creatures, capable of carrying large weapons while possessing maneuverability that few others can match. They can forcefully carry their own Zerg that has not yet fallen to the ground to enhance the mobility of the slow Zerg on the battlefield.</ARA_Skyraider_Base.description>
  <ARA_Skyraider_Hivelord.label>Subspecies-Lord Species</ARA_Skyraider_Hivelord.label>
  <ARA_Skyraider_Hivelord.description>This Arachne Sky Seed has obtained Bazhao, and will throw Sky Nest Seed auxiliary insects at the enemy. These sensitive auxiliary insects will scatter around to hunt the target after landing.</ARA_Skyraider_Hivelord.description>
  <ARA_Skyraider_Empthrower.label>Subspecies-Hurricane species</ARA_Skyraider_Empthrower.label>
  <ARA_Skyraider_Empthrower.description>This Arachne Sky Seed has obtained Bazhao, and will throw Magnetic Storm Seed auxiliary insects at the enemy. These auxiliary insects will scatter after landing, and release EMP in a suicidal attack to fight against the enemy mechanical race.</ARA_Skyraider_Empthrower.description>
  <ARA_Praetorian_Base.label>Queen's Throat</ARA_Praetorian_Base.label>
  <ARA_Praetorian_Base.description>The Arachne Guards are agents of will personally cultivated by the Queen. Not only do they have superb shooting skills, but they can also command friendly troops on the battlefield to make them stronger.</ARA_Praetorian_Base.description>
  <ARA_Praetorian_Navigator.label>Subspecies - pilot species</ARA_Praetorian_Navigator.label>
  <ARA_Praetorian_Navigator.description>This Arachne Guard species has obtained the Bahyao. Although it has lost its direct combat ability, it can command the aerial beasts and insects and crush the enemy with the absolute air superiority of the insect swarms.</ARA_Praetorian_Navigator.description>

</LanguageData>