<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
<ARA_Myrmecocystus_Production_InsectJelly.label>insect nectar chamber</ARA_Myrmecocystus_Production_InsectJelly.label>
<ARA_Myrmecocystus_Production_InsectJelly.description>This honeycan species produces honey to feed its insect colony.</ARA_Myrmecocystus_Production_InsectJelly.description>
<ARA_Myrmecocystus_Production_Medicine.label>Subspecies - Healing species</ARA_Myrmecocystus_Production_Medicine.label>
<ARA_Myrmecocystus_Production_Medicine.description>This Arachne honeycan species has acquired a moss and no longer produces nectar, but instead produces medicines and chemicals that are rare for the hive. It is also capable of controlling pseudonematode parasites.</ARA_Myrmecocystus_Production_Medicine.description>
<ARA_Myrmecocystus_Production_Fuel.label>Subspecies – deflagration species</ARA_Myrmecocystus_Production_Fuel.label>
<ARA_Myrmecocystus_Production_Fuel.description>This Arachne honeycan species has evolved to no longer produce nectar, but instead periodically generates a compound fuel that is in short supply in its nest.It can also shoot flames to fight off enemies.</ARA_Myrmecocystus_Production_Fuel.description>
<ARA_Fighter_Base.label>insect nest warrior</ARA_Fighter_Base.label>
<ARA_Fighter_Base.description>Arachne's warrior bugs can transform their bodies into the most powerful weapons.Once their techniques are unlocked, they can learn a variety of skills.</ARA_Fighter_Base.description>
<ARA_Fighter_Invisibility.label>Subspecies - Pursuit species</ARA_Fighter_Invisibility.label>
<ARA_Fighter_Invisibility.description>Evolved warrior species have acquired specialized iridescent cells that cover their entire bodies. These cells, containing nanocrystals, can refract light and remain permanently invisible until they attack. They also have improved close combat capabilities, although their compound eyes have degenerated, making shooting difficult.</ARA_Fighter_Invisibility.description>
<ARA_Fighter_Genestealer.label>subspecies-variant</ARA_Fighter_Genestealer.label>
<ARA_Fighter_Genestealer.description>The mutants are like walking genetic archives. They are no longer warriors fighting blood and sword among the insect swarm, but are dedicated to extracting and refining superior genes from prisoners and slaves, and imparting them to high-quality individuals within the insect swarm.</ARA_Fighter_Genestealer.description>
<ARA_Smokepop_Base.label>biological chimney</ARA_Smokepop_Base.label>
<ARA_Smokepop_Base.description>The Stray Mist species is a large body of the Arachne insect family, and not only does it have a thick outer shell, but it can also emit a gas that covers the battlefield from its abdomen filled with information elements.This allows it to attract small scale insects and make them launch a fierce attack against the enemy.</ARA_Smokepop_Base.description>
<ARA_Smokepop_Production_Bacterium.label>Subspecies - Breeding species</ARA_Smokepop_Production_Bacterium.label>
<ARA_Smokepop_Production_Bacterium.description>This Arachne mist species has acquired a moss, and its front shell has fallen off, making it unable to eject information elements.Instead, it has acquired the ability to produce activated bacteria.One breeding species produces 5 activated bacteria per day.</ARA_Smokepop_Production_Bacterium.description>
<ARA_Smokepop_Creeper.label>Subspecies - Kingworm species</ARA_Smokepop_Creeper.label>
<ARA_Smokepop_Creeper.description>This Arachne mist species has already awakened, and can deploy creeps while moving, modifying the terrain around the nest, and creating invasion routes to other colonies.Furthermore, it has acquired the ability to project fungi towards the enemy.</ARA_Smokepop_Creeper.description>
<ARA_ShieldHead_Base.label>hard-shelled species</ARA_ShieldHead_Base.label>
<ARA_ShieldHead_Base.description>The shieldhead species is small and not as intimidating as the large Arachnidae, but it has sufficient defense power due to the carapace that covers its entire body.The shell has the property of overgrowing and falling off, and the shed shell can be used for nest construction.One shieldhead species produces 15 shell elements per day.</ARA_ShieldHead_Base.description>
<ARA_ShieldHead_Protector.label>Subspecies - nest guard species</ARA_ShieldHead_Protector.label>
<ARA_ShieldHead_Protector.description>This Arachne Shieldhead species has acquired the 拔耀, which has improved its combat ability.It can also defeat enemies with a powerful lunge attack.</ARA_ShieldHead_Protector.description>
<ARA_ShieldHead_HiveBuilder.label>Subspecies - commercial species</ARA_ShieldHead_HiveBuilder.label>
<ARA_ShieldHead_HiveBuilder.description>This Arachne shieldhead species has evolved and gained powerful production and construction abilities.The shieldhead species produces an additional 15 pieces of chitin per day.</ARA_ShieldHead_HiveBuilder.description>
<ARA_Skyraider_Base.label>flying behemoth</ARA_Skyraider_Base.label>
<ARA_Skyraider_Base.description>Arachne is the ruler of the skies.They have large, agile and deadly bodies, and are highly maneuverable while carrying large weapons.</ARA_Skyraider_Base.description>
<ARA_Skyraider_Hivelord.label>Subspecies - lord type</ARA_Skyraider_Hivelord.label>
<ARA_Skyraider_Hivelord.description>This Arachne sky species has evolved to throw sky seed insects.After dropping, these agile insects disperse and hunt targets in various places.</ARA_Skyraider_Hivelord.description>
<ARA_Skyraider_Empthrower.label>Subspecies - Storm species</ARA_Skyraider_Empthrower.label>
<ARA_Skyraider_Empthrower.description>This Arachne sky species has evolved to throw magnetic storm seed insects. These insects release EMP through suicide attacks to counter opposing mechanoids.</ARA_Skyraider_Empthrower.description>
<ARA_Praetorian_Base.label>Empress's Throat</ARA_Praetorian_Base.label>
<ARA_Praetorian_Base.description>Arachne is an agent of will that was directly cultivated by the Empress.Not only does she have excellent shooting skills, but she can also command her allies on the battlefield and make them more powerful.</ARA_Praetorian_Base.description>
<ARA_Praetorian_Navigator.label>Subspecies - Towing species</ARA_Praetorian_Navigator.label>
<ARA_Praetorian_Navigator.description>This Arachne Guard has evolved, and although it has lost the ability to fight directly, it is able to command aerial beasts and crush its enemies with absolute air supremacy.</ARA_Praetorian_Navigator.description>
<ARA_Slayer_Base.label>beast of violence</ARA_Slayer_Base.label>
<ARA_Slayer_Base.description>Arachne butchers are a special type of beast insect. Their intelligence rating is significantly lower than that of their brothers and sisters, but in return they have advantages unparalleled to other insect races: their huge bodies and thick carapaces. This allows them to withstand all attacks and crush enemy defensive positions like a hammer.</ARA_Slayer_Base.description>
<ARA_WeaponSmith_Base.label>hive maintainer</ARA_WeaponSmith_Base.label>
<ARA_WeaponSmith_Base.description>Arachne craftsmen are hard workers, maintaining the entire nest structure and keeping it in top working condition.</ARA_WeaponSmith_Base.description>
</LanguageData>
