<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
<Arachnae_Queen_BS_Child_1.title>instinctive hunter</Arachnae_Queen_BS_Child_1.title>
<Arachnae_Queen_BS_Child_1.titleShort>instinctive hunter</Arachnae_Queen_BS_Child_1.titleShort>
<Arachnae_Queen_BS_Child_1.description>{PAWN_nameDef} was born as an empress of the Arachne insect race and was kept in a breeding chamber with over a hundred sisters.\n\nWhen the beeswax sealing off the breeding chamber was removed by worker bees, {PAWN_nameDef} WN_nameDef} stood up covered in blood and bodily fluids. At her feet lay the chipped limbs and mangled corpses of her fallen sisters. She was the only victor in the ordeal of survival.</Arachnae_Queen_BS_Child_1.description>
<Arachnae_Queen_BS_Adult_1.title>apprentice empress</Arachnae_Queen_BS_Adult_1.title>
<Arachnae_Queen_BS_Adult_1.titleShort>apprentice empress</Arachnae_Queen_BS_Adult_1.titleShort>
<Arachnae_Queen_BS_Adult_1.description>Once {PAWN_nameDef} had successfully grown up in the nest, she left her home and set out for the unknown, where she began preparing to build her own power.\n\n{PAWN_nameDef} understands that she is still weak, and unlike her other spoiled sisters, she tries to do what she can with her own hands.</Arachnae_Queen_BS_Adult_1.description>
<Arachnae_Node_BS_Child_1.title>Arachne insect</Arachnae_Node_BS_Child_1.title>
<Arachnae_Node_BS_Child_1.titleShort>Administrative insect</Arachnae_Node_BS_Child_1.titleShort>
<Arachnae_Node_BS_Child_1.description>{PAWN_nameDef} is an Arachne Insect. This class of Arachne Insects is the core of the hive, and at the same time receives command from the Empresses, they also lead their subordinates, the Insects. From the time they are born, they are each given a different mission, and they dedicate their entire short lives to serve the Insects.</Arachnae_Node_BS_Child_1.description>
<Arachnae_MimicNematode_BS_Child_1.title>Arachne pseudoline species</Arachnae_MimicNematode_BS_Child_1.title>
<Arachnae_MimicNematode_BS_Child_1.titleShort>pseudoline type</Arachnae_MimicNematode_BS_Child_1.titleShort>
<Arachnae_MimicNematode_BS_Child_1.description>{PAWN_nameDef} is an Arachne Pseudoline species.They are different from normal insects, and are parasitic creatures that inhabit the bodies of intelligent creatures and manipulate their bodies.</Arachnae_MimicNematode_BS_Child_1.description>
<Arachnae_MimicNematode_BS_Adult_1.title>arachne pseudolinear</Arachnae_MimicNematode_BS_Adult_1.title>
<Arachnae_MimicNematode_BS_Adult_1.titleShort>pseudolinear field</Arachnae_MimicNematode_BS_Adult_1.titleShort>
<Arachnae_MimicNematode_BS_Adult_1.description>{PAWN_nameDef} is an Arachne Pseudoray.It was created as a body parasitic and controlled by the Arachne Pseudoray, has no will of its own, and is unable to live independently apart from the Pseudoray's parasitism.</Arachnae_MimicNematode_BS_Adult_1.description>
<Arachnae_Node_BS_Adult_Myrmecocystus.title>Arachne honey can type</Arachnae_Node_BS_Adult_Myrmecocystus.title>
<Arachnae_Node_BS_Adult_Myrmecocystus.titleShort>honey can kind</Arachnae_Node_BS_Adult_Myrmecocystus.titleShort>
<Arachnae_Node_BS_Adult_Myrmecocystus.description>{PAWN_nameDef} is an insect of the Arachne honeycan species. Through selective gene expression, she has developed an enlarged stomach can and complex mouthparts. It can be converted into a nutritional liquid called nectar and supplied to other insects.\n\n{PAWN_nameDef} is powerless in battle and slow in movement. Its fragile and bloated body is unable to evade most attacks.</Arachnae_Node_BS_Adult_Myrmecocystus.description>
<Arachnae_Node_BS_Adult_ShieldHead.title>Arachne shield species</Arachnae_Node_BS_Adult_ShieldHead.title>
<Arachnae_Node_BS_Adult_ShieldHead.titleShort>shieldhead species</Arachnae_Node_BS_Adult_ShieldHead.titleShort>
<Arachnae_Node_BS_Adult_ShieldHead.description>{PAWN_nameDef} is a control insect of the Arachne Shield-head species. Shield-heads are heavily armored Arachne bugs with thick overgrown shells. In addition to producing shell elements, they have appendages to connect their weapon organs, and use their natural armor and swarm armament to protect their nests.</Arachnae_Node_BS_Adult_ShieldHead.description>
<Arachnae_Node_BS_Adult_WeaponSmith.title>Arachne craft type</Arachnae_Node_BS_Adult_WeaponSmith.title>
<Arachnae_Node_BS_Adult_WeaponSmith.titleShort>Craft type</Arachnae_Node_BS_Adult_WeaponSmith.titleShort>
<Arachnae_Node_BS_Adult_WeaponSmith.description>{PAWN_nameDef} is a control insect of the Arachne craft species. In order to increase the combat power of the nest, it can produce a special moth that hatches weapon organs.\n\n{PAWN_nameDef} can manipulate weapon organs, but it has a tendency to be extremely afraid of getting hurt. Therefore, it tries to avoid being on the front lines of battle as much as possible.</Arachnae_Node_BS_Adult_WeaponSmith.description>
<Arachnae_Node_BS_Adult_Fighter.title>Arachne warrior type</Arachnae_Node_BS_Adult_Fighter.title>
<Arachnae_Node_BS_Adult_Fighter.titleShort>warrior species</Arachnae_Node_BS_Adult_Fighter.titleShort>
<Arachnae_Node_BS_Adult_Fighter.description>{PAWN_nameDef} is a control insect of the Arachne warrior type. It can hunt and transport, and has high aptitude for both close-range and ranged combat. Although it cannot hatch insects under normal conditions, it can shoot out the acid insects like bullets and suppress the enemy's firepower at the cost of its short life.</Arachnae_Node_BS_Adult_Fighter.description>
<Arachnae_Node_BS_Adult_Smokepop.title>Arachne mist type</Arachnae_Node_BS_Adult_Smokepop.title>
<Arachnae_Node_BS_Adult_Smokepop.titleShort>Stray mist type</Arachnae_Node_BS_Adult_Smokepop.titleShort>
<Arachnae_Node_BS_Adult_Smokepop.description>{PAWN_nameDef} is an insect of the Arachne mist species. It is a rare giant that can be equipped with large weapon organs, and its thick shell makes it impenetrable to common firearms.\n\nAdditionally, she has a large mist cavity, from which she can spray a sticky white smoke that inhibits combustion over a wide area through multiple biological injection tubes. This allows her to hide the insect swarm's assault from enemy artillery.</Arachnae_Node_BS_Adult_Smokepop.description>
<Arachnae_Node_BS_Adult_Skyraider.title>Arachne air raid type</Arachnae_Node_BS_Adult_Skyraider.title>
<Arachnae_Node_BS_Adult_Skyraider.titleShort>air raid type</Arachnae_Node_BS_Adult_Skyraider.titleShort>
<Arachnae_Node_BS_Adult_Skyraider.description>{PAWN_nameDef} is the control insect of the Arachne air-raid species.The air-raid species is the most elite of the Arachne insects, and because of its outstanding flight ability, it dominates the skies of its nest.</Arachnae_Node_BS_Adult_Skyraider.description>
<Arachnae_Node_BS_Adult_Facehugger.title>Arachne protozoa species</Arachnae_Node_BS_Adult_Facehugger.title>
<Arachnae_Node_BS_Adult_Facehugger.titleShort>protozoan species</Arachnae_Node_BS_Adult_Facehugger.titleShort>
<Arachnae_Node_BS_Adult_Facehugger.description>{PAWN_nameDef} is the master insect of the Arachne species. She extends her own neural connections into the body of her victims and takes control of their bodies. During control, the higher skill proficiency between the species and the host is applied, but any proficiency gained during the parasitic period is not transferred to the species upon withdrawal.</Arachnae_Node_BS_Adult_Facehugger.description>
<Arachnae_Node_BS_Adult_NeuroSwarm.title>Arachne weaving species</Arachnae_Node_BS_Adult_NeuroSwarm.title>
<Arachnae_Node_BS_Adult_NeuroSwarm.titleShort>Weaving area species</Arachnae_Node_BS_Adult_NeuroSwarm.titleShort>
<Arachnae_Node_BS_Adult_NeuroSwarm.description>{PAWN_nameDef} is a supervisory insect of the Arachne Origen species.Although they are under the supervision of the Empress species, Oriens are highly intelligent and have a strong sense of self.They connect each other's nerves to form neural networks that allow them to perform complex research and calculations.\n\nAs they are almost imperceptible to external stimuli while performing computational tasks, Oriari are extremely important protection targets for the insect population.</Arachnae_Node_BS_Adult_NeuroSwarm.description>
<Arachnae_Node_BS_Adult_Praetorian.title>Arachne forbidden species</Arachnae_Node_BS_Adult_Praetorian.title>
<Arachnae_Node_BS_Adult_Praetorian.titleShort>Forbidden species</Arachnae_Node_BS_Adult_Praetorian.titleShort>
<Arachnae_Node_BS_Adult_Praetorian.description>{PAWN_nameDef} is a control insect of the Arachne Forbidden Guard species. They are elite soldiers who serve the Empress, and are tasked with enforcing the Empress's will. They skillfully manipulate remote weapons and are able to gracefully slaughter their enemies, as well as hatch a large number of Acidic Insects and build a line of defense.</Arachnae_Node_BS_Adult_Praetorian.description>
</LanguageData>
