<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>

  <ARA_Huge_Weapon.label>Huge Weapon Organ</ARA_Huge_Weapon.label>
  <ARA_Huge_Weapon.description>This weapon organ is quite large and can only be used by large Arachnae Swarm Nodes (body size greater than 2.0).</ARA_Huge_Weapon.description>

  <ARA_Weapon_Damage_Acid.label>Arachnae Acid</ARA_Weapon_Damage_Acid.label>
  <ARA_Weapon_Damage_Acid.description>When this weapon organ's projectile hits an enemy, it leaves acid on the target that causes sustained damage.</ARA_Weapon_Damage_Acid.description>

  <ARA_Weapon_Damage_Toxid.label>Arachnae Toxin</ARA_Weapon_Damage_Toxid.label>
  <ARA_Weapon_Damage_Toxid.description>When this weapon organ's projectile hits an enemy, it injects a toxin into the target, causing poisoning.</ARA_Weapon_Damage_Toxid.description>

  <ARA_Weapon_Damage_Spawn.label>Arachnae Sub-Hive</ARA_Weapon_Damage_Spawn.label>
  <ARA_Weapon_Damage_Spawn.description>The primary attack method of this weapon organ is releasing auxiliary insects. Some will throw the auxiliary insects directly at the enemy, while others will cause the auxiliary insects to track and latch onto enemy forces to deal damage.</ARA_Weapon_Damage_Spawn.description>

  <ARA_Weapon_ChainReload.label>Chain Reload</ARA_Weapon_ChainReload.label>
  <ARA_Weapon_ChainReload.description>This weapon organ releases hormones with each attack to speed up the metabolic rate, which manifests as increased firing speed and reload speed.</ARA_Weapon_ChainReload.description>

  <ARA_Weapon_OverPenetrate.label>Over-Penetration</ARA_Weapon_OverPenetrate.label>
  <ARA_Weapon_OverPenetrate.description>When this weapon organ's projectile hits an enemy, it does not stop but penetrates all enemies in its path, dealing damage.</ARA_Weapon_OverPenetrate.description>

  <ARA_Weapon_Damage_LightingChain.label>Psionic Lightning Chain</ARA_Weapon_Damage_LightingChain.label>
  <ARA_Weapon_Damage_LightingChain.description>This weapon organ fires a lightning chain that bounces between enemies, dealing damage.</ARA_Weapon_Damage_LightingChain.description>

  <ARA_Weapon_Damage_Icez.label>Extreme Freeze Shatter</ARA_Weapon_Damage_Icez.label>
  <ARA_Weapon_Damage_Icez.description>This weapon organ freezes enemies, a state that makes the target's body structure extremely fragile. As this effect deepens, the "freezing" damage threshold required to destroy body parts will be significantly reduced.</ARA_Weapon_Damage_Icez.description>

  <ARA_Weapon_Damage_FrostExplode.label>Frost Explosion</ARA_Weapon_Damage_FrostExplode.label>
  <ARA_Weapon_Damage_FrostExplode.description>The frost mist fired by this weapon organ can contaminate enemies; contaminated enemies will explode again.</ARA_Weapon_Damage_FrostExplode.description>

</LanguageData>