<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
<ArachnaeQueen_Race.label>Arachne type</ArachnaeQueen_Race.label>
<ArachnaeQueen_Race.description>The Arachne Taitan species is one of the subspecies of the Empress species, and belongs to the Arachne Taitan tentacles.They command the main group, which is the most robust and adaptable of the Arachne insect group, and are responsible for maintaining the front line on the battlefield. \n\nThe Empress of the Taitan species not only has the special technique of Taitan tentacles, but she also has a powerful carapace as a layer of defense, and can attack enemies that get close to her with stomps and high melee attack power.</ArachnaeQueen_Race.description>
<ArachnaeQueen_Race.alienRace.generalSettings.alienPartGenerator.colorChannels.0.name>skin</ArachnaeQueen_Race.alienRace.generalSettings.alienPartGenerator.colorChannels.0.name>
<ArachnaeQueen_Race.alienRace.generalSettings.alienPartGenerator.colorChannels.1.name>hair</ArachnaeQueen_Race.alienRace.generalSettings.alienPartGenerator.colorChannels.1.name>
<ArachnaeQueen_Race.tools.0.label>top of head</ArachnaeQueen_Race.tools.0.label>
<ArachnaeQueen_Race.tools.1.label>Trampling</ArachnaeQueen_Race.tools.1.label>
<ArachnaeQueen_Race.tools.2.label>leg puncture</ArachnaeQueen_Race.tools.2.label>
<ArachnaeQueen_Race.tools.3.label>force attack</ArachnaeQueen_Race.tools.3.label>
<ArachnaeQueen_Race_Neurotyrant.label>Arachne spirit sucker</ArachnaeQueen_Race_Neurotyrant.label>
<ArachnaeQueen_Race_Neurotyrant.description>The Arachne spirit-sucking species is one of the subspecies of the Empress species and belongs to Arachne's psychic tentacles.They maintain the communication of the psychic network in the insect tribe's burrows, and serve as relay points to connect the Empress species in each war zone and their burrows.\n \nSpirits are natural-born psychic masters, and their powerful psychic abilities allow them to dominate the battlefield with supernatural power.In addition, by absorbing local creatures one after another, their psychic abilities undergo adaptive evolution.</ArachnaeQueen_Race_Neurotyrant.description>
<ArachnaeQueen_Race_Neurotyrant.alienRace.generalSettings.alienPartGenerator.colorChannels.0.name>skin</ArachnaeQueen_Race_Neurotyrant.alienRace.generalSettings.alienPartGenerator.colorChannels.0.name>
<ArachnaeQueen_Race_Neurotyrant.alienRace.generalSettings.alienPartGenerator.colorChannels.1.name>hair</ArachnaeQueen_Race_Neurotyrant.alienRace.generalSettings.alienPartGenerator.colorChannels.1.name>
<ArachnaeQueen_Race_Neurotyrant.tools.0.label>Limb puncture</ArachnaeQueen_Race_Neurotyrant.tools.0.label>
</LanguageData>
