<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
<ARA_Huge_Weapon.label>large weapon organ</ARA_Huge_Weapon.label>
<ARA_Huge_Weapon.description>This weapon organ is extremely large and can only be used by large Arachne insects with a body size of over 2.0 cm.</ARA_Huge_Weapon.description>
<ARA_Weapon_Damage_Acid.label>arachnic acid solution</ARA_Weapon_Damage_Acid.label>
<ARA_Weapon_Damage_Acid.description>When a bullet from this weapon hits an enemy, it leaves an acidic liquid on the target's body, causing lasting damage.</ARA_Weapon_Damage_Acid.description>
<ARA_Weapon_Damage_Toxid.label>arachne toxin</ARA_Weapon_Damage_Toxid.label>
<ARA_Weapon_Damage_Toxid.description>When a bullet from this weapon hits an enemy, it injects toxins into the target's body, poisoning it.</ARA_Weapon_Damage_Toxid.description>
<ARA_Weapon_Damage_Spawn.label>Arachne secondary nest</ARA_Weapon_Damage_Spawn.label>
<ARA_Weapon_Damage_Spawn.description>The main attack method of this weapon is the release of secondary insects, some of which are directly projected onto enemy lines, and some of which track and attach themselves to the enemy, causing damage.</ARA_Weapon_Damage_Spawn.description>
<ARA_Weapon_ChainReload.label>chain reload</ARA_Weapon_ChainReload.label>
<ARA_Weapon_ChainReload.description>With each attack, this weapon organ releases hormones that increase metabolic rate, resulting in increased firing and reloading speeds.</ARA_Weapon_ChainReload.description>
<ARA_Weapon_OverPenetrate.label>excessive penetration</ARA_Weapon_OverPenetrate.label>
<ARA_Weapon_OverPenetrate.description>The bullets of this weapon do not stop even when they hit an enemy, and they penetrate and damage all enemies in their path.</ARA_Weapon_OverPenetrate.description>
<ARA_Weapon_Damage_LightingChain.label>psychic lightning chain</ARA_Weapon_Damage_LightingChain.label>
<ARA_Weapon_Damage_LightingChain.description>This weapon fires lightning chains that bounce between enemies, causing damage.</ARA_Weapon_Damage_LightingChain.description>
<ARA_Weapon_Damage_Icez.label>Rapid cooling crushing</ARA_Weapon_Damage_Icez.label>
<ARA_Weapon_Damage_Icez.description>This weapon freezes the enemy. This condition leaves the target's body structures extremely vulnerable. As the effect deepens, the threshold of "freezing" damage required to destroy a body part is significantly lowered.</ARA_Weapon_Damage_Icez.description>
<ARA_Weapon_Damage_FrostExplode.label>freeze explosion</ARA_Weapon_Damage_FrostExplode.label>
<ARA_Weapon_Damage_FrostExplode.description>The frost mist fired by this weapon attaches to enemies, causing them to explode again.</ARA_Weapon_Damage_FrostExplode.description>
</LanguageData>
