<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
<ARA_Bodystocking_White.label>Arachne body stockings (white)</ARA_Bodystocking_White.label>
<ARA_Bodystocking_White.description>This is a decorative fabric of the Arachne insect group, and is not particularly useful for the insect group.</ARA_Bodystocking_White.description>
<ARA_Bodystocking_Black.label>Arachne body stockings (black)</ARA_Bodystocking_Black.label>
<ARA_Bodystocking_Black.description>This is a decorative fabric of the Arachne insect group, and is not particularly useful for the insect group.</ARA_Bodystocking_Black.description>
<ARA_Latex_Catsuit.label>arachne tight suit</ARA_Latex_Catsuit.label>
<ARA_Latex_Catsuit.description>This is a decorative fabric of the Arachne insect group, and is not particularly useful for the insect group.</ARA_Latex_Catsuit.description>
<ARA_Pantyhose_Black.label>Arachne stockings (black)</ARA_Pantyhose_Black.label>
<ARA_Pantyhose_Black.description>This is a decorative fabric of the Arachne insect group, and is not particularly useful for the insect group.</ARA_Pantyhose_Black.description>
<ARA_Pantyhose_White.label>Arachne stockings (white)</ARA_Pantyhose_White.label>
<ARA_Pantyhose_White.description>This is a decorative fabric of the Arachne insect group, and is not particularly useful for the insect group.</ARA_Pantyhose_White.description>
<ARA_Maid_Uniform.label>Arachne maid uniform</ARA_Maid_Uniform.label>
<ARA_Maid_Uniform.description>A type of fabric worn by Arachne insects, the design is form-fitting, lightweight, and increases the speed of work on Arachne creeps.It perfectly embodies the symbol of their eternal service to the insect nest.</ARA_Maid_Uniform.description>
<ARA_Maid_Dress.label>Arachne armed maid uniform</ARA_Maid_Dress.label>
<ARA_Maid_Dress.description>A type of fabric worn by Arachne insects, with a classic and elegant design, which allows them to maintain a stable position on the creep and improve their shooting accuracy.This is the perfect embodiment of their eternal service to the insect nest.</ARA_Maid_Dress.description>
<ARA_Daily_Wear.label>Arachne everyday clothes</ARA_Daily_Wear.label>
<ARA_Daily_Wear.description>A type of fabric worn by Arachne insects that increases the speed of the caravan's movement on creeps, and slowly slows down when the caravan leaves.This cute everyday clothing, combined with the mind control effect of the insects, has the power to make humans admire how cute it is.</ARA_Daily_Wear.description>
<ARA_Bunny_Girl_Uniform.label>arachne bunny girl clothes</ARA_Bunny_Girl_Uniform.label>
<ARA_Bunny_Girl_Uniform.description>A type of fabric worn by Arachne insects that hugs the contours of the body and increases movement speed on Arachne creep.</ARA_Bunny_Girl_Uniform.description>
<ARA_Nurse_Uniform.label>arachne nurse uniform</ARA_Nurse_Uniform.label>
<ARA_Nurse_Uniform.description>A type of textile worn by the Arachne insects, whose design is inspired by elements of the Red Cross in human society, but the insects themselves do not understand its meaning.There are multiple healing conduits inside the fabric, allowing the Arachne insects to extract nutrients from the creep and heal other individuals.</ARA_Nurse_Uniform.description>
<ARA_Nightdress.label>arachne nightgown</ARA_Nightdress.label>
<ARA_Nightdress.description>It is a type of fabric worn by the Arachnid insect, which can further increase its resting efficiency on the creep.Sleeping is one of the few demands that the insect nest requires frequent maintenance, so the value of this fabric is obvious.</ARA_Nightdress.description>
<ARA_Eveningdress.label>arachne evening dress</ARA_Eveningdress.label>
<ARA_Eveningdress.description>A type of textile worn by Arachne insects that has a noble and enchanting design and is imbued with powerful psychic energy.This textile can amplify the wearer's psychic abilities.</ARA_Eveningdress.description>
<ARA_Wedding_Dress.label>arachne wedding dress</ARA_Wedding_Dress.label>
<ARA_Wedding_Dress.description>A type of fabric worn by the Arachne insect, which has overwhelming strength and can use the power of creeps to seize hearts and direct enemy fire toward allies.</ARA_Wedding_Dress.description>
<ARA_Dragoon_Uniform.label>Arachne Guard Uniform</ARA_Dragoon_Uniform.label>
<ARA_Dragoon_Uniform.description>A type of fabric worn by the most advanced warriors of the Arachnoid group, it emits a deafening roar and conveys an unexpected sense of majesty—but all illusions of beauty disappear when they tear apart their fellows with their clanking shears.</ARA_Dragoon_Uniform.description>
</LanguageData>
