<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <ARA_InsectWall.label>Arachne's Carapace Wall</ARA_InsectWall.label>
  <ARA_InsectWall.description>The walls formed by the Arachne worker bees mixed with hard materials and chitin are very hard, but they don’t look very beautiful and do not need to be built on the Arachne carpet.</ARA_InsectWall.description>
  <ARA_SmoothedInsectWall.label>Smooth Arachne Carapace Wall</ARA_SmoothedInsectWall.label>
  <ARA_SmoothedInsectWall.description>Arachne worker bees mixed hard materials and chitin to form a wall. The Zerg carefully polished this wall, making it hard in texture and much more beautiful in appearance.</ARA_SmoothedInsectWall.description>
  <ARA_InsectDoor.label>Arachne Carapace Door</ARA_InsectDoor.label>
  <ARA_InsectDoor.description>The main body of the entrance to the Arachne Hive is made of a mixture of hard materials and chitin, and the opening and closing mechanism is an Arachne tissue structure without complete consciousness, which allows it to open and close automatically without the need to build on the Arachne carpet.</ARA_InsectDoor.description>
  <ARA_SmoothedInsectDoor.label>Smooth Arachne Carapace Door</ARA_SmoothedInsectDoor.label>
  <ARA_SmoothedInsectDoor.description>The main body of the entrance to the Arachne Hive is made of a mixture of hard materials and chitin, and the opening and closing mechanism is an Arachne tissue structure without complete consciousness, which allows it to open and close automatically without the need to build on the Arachne carpet. \n\nIt has been polished by the insect swarm and is now smooth and beautiful.</ARA_SmoothedInsectDoor.description>
  <ARA_Tumor.label>Arachne's tumor</ARA_Tumor.label>
  <ARA_Tumor.description>The fungus will emit a faint light to illuminate Arachne's nest. In addition to lighting, it will also spread the fungus over a large area on the ground, allowing worker bees to build more Arachne structures. No need to build on Arachne creep.</ARA_Tumor.description>
  <ARA_Tumor_SunLamp.label>Arachne photoma</ARA_Tumor_SunLamp.label>
  <ARA_Tumor_SunLamp.description>A bacterial tumor is larger than an ordinary bacterial tumor, and the internal light-emitting organ is unimaginably bright. It can support the lighting conditions of crops, but its lifespan is much shorter than an ordinary bacterial tumor, and it will not spread the bacterial carpet.</ARA_Tumor_SunLamp.description>
  <ARA_NodeNest.label>Arachneid's Lair</ARA_NodeNest.label>
  <ARA_NodeNest.description>The nest for the Arachneid worm to inhabit, the "quilt" formed by chitin carapace, muscle and connective tissue, is a very good place for the worm to replenish energy.</ARA_NodeNest.description>
  <ARA_ResearchBench.label>Arachne Research Station</ARA_ResearchBench.label>
  <ARA_ResearchBench.description>A living structure for the Arachne zerg to study, allowing the swarm to explore mutation and evolutionary directions to their heart's content.</ARA_ResearchBench.description>
  <ARA_SmartThermostat.label>Arachne</ARA_SmartThermostat.label>
  <ARA_SmartThermostat.description>An Arachne with only basic reflexes will try to maintain the temperature of the room toward which its tail is directed through gas exchange. Must be mounted on the wall like a cooler.</ARA_SmartThermostat.description>
  <ARA_Table1x2c.label>Arachne's Table (1x2)</ARA_Table1x2c.label>
  <ARA_Table1x2c.description>The strange table seems to be made of living tissue such as rocks and tentacles, and it glows slightly because of the luminous tissue on its body.</ARA_Table1x2c.description>
  <ARA_Chair.label>Swarm Chair</ARA_Chair.label>
  <ARA_Chair.description>The strange chair seems to be made of living tissue such as rocks and tentacles, and it glows because of the luminous tissue on its body.</ARA_Chair.description>
  <ARA_Column.label>Pillar of the Swarm</ARA_Column.label>
  <ARA_Column.description>The living tissue grown from the tentacles in the Arachne swarm can support the roof from collapsing, emit a wide range of light, and is much stronger than ordinary support columns.</ARA_Column.description>
  <ARA_Shelf.label>Insect Swarm Storage Point</ARA_Shelf.label>
  <ARA_Shelf.description>Something similar to a human item rack is actually just a hole dug by the Zerg in the ground to store things - but thanks to the four tentacles with embedded micro-neural networks, the Zerg can quickly find what they need in the messy pile of items.</ARA_Shelf.description>
  <ARA_SkillTraining_Building.label>Insect climbing frame</ARA_SkillTraining_Building.label>
  <ARA_SkillTraining_Building.description>A living organization for idle Arachne zerg to kill time, so that they can practice their skills while killing time, so as not to bother the hive mind by sending idle signals all the time.</ARA_SkillTraining_Building.description>
  <ARA_Hibernate_Sac.label>Arachne's hypnotic body</ARA_Hibernate_Sac.label>
  <ARA_Hibernate_Sac.description>Living tissue formed by the Arachne Zerg entering a dormant state.</ARA_Hibernate_Sac.description>
</LanguageData>
