<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
<ARA_InsectJelly.label>Arachne insect honey</ARA_InsectJelly.label>
<ARA_InsectJelly.description>A jelly that is stored and used as food by the Arachnid tribe, and is the only food for many of the Arachnid tribe. It is smooth, thick, non-perishable, and satisfies the eater's desire for entertainment. Due to its unique biological properties, it can be eaten by non-Arachne tribes and does not cause food poisoning.</ARA_InsectJelly.description>
<ARA_NutrientPasteMeal.label>Arachne honey crystal cake</ARA_NutrientPasteMeal.label>
<ARA_NutrientPasteMeal.description>It is a sticky "cake" synthesized from insect nectar, and is mixed with information elements that activate insect activity.Not only does it help insect nests withstand harsh environments, but its unique flavor is also liked by humans.</ARA_NutrientPasteMeal.description>
<ARA_Carapace.label>crustacean</ARA_Carapace.label>
<ARA_Carapace.description>This is a shell element stripped from a part of the Arachne insect family that has a thick shell.It is lightweight but not very durable, and is used for a variety of purposes inside the insect's nest.</ARA_Carapace.description>
<ARA_Activated_Bacterium.label>activated giant bacteria</ARA_Activated_Bacterium.label>
<ARA_Activated_Bacterium.description>It is an extreme microbial community that has been domesticated and modified by the Arachne insect tribe.It has strong biocatalytic ability and corrosion assimilation ability, and is an essential material for the high-grade equipment of many insect tribes.</ARA_Activated_Bacterium.description>
<ARA_Gene_Essence.label>essence</ARA_Gene_Essence.label>
<ARA_Gene_Essence.description>It is a foreign genetic material stored in the bodies of small auxiliary insects, the Arachne spp., and is extremely fragile. It is usually obtained from prisoners using essence extraction tanks, and is one of the important resources for the Arachne insect population.</ARA_Gene_Essence.description>
</LanguageData>
