<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
<ARA_SpawnFlyOverTest.label>Mothership summon</ARA_SpawnFlyOverTest.label>
<ARA_SpawnFlyOverTest.description>Summons the Hive Mothership and activates the final event chain of insect swarm invasion (for testing purposes. Any misuse is at your own risk).</ARA_SpawnFlyOverTest.description>
<ARA_Spawn_ARA_HiveCorvette_Rocket.label>Heavenly Shrine Cruise: Acid Burning Cannon Strafing</ARA_Spawn_ARA_HiveCorvette_Rocket.label>
<ARA_Spawn_ARA_HiveCorvette_Rocket.description>The Towing Type commands the Arachne Heavenly Shrine Beast Bug, and attacks the target area with a Rapid Disaster Gun with Arachne Bug Acid effect while sweeping through the battlefield at high speed.\n\nDuring flight, the Bloodrock Spikes Cannon is used to attack the enemies it encounters, but because the attack area is limited, the Bloodrock Spikes Cannon only attacks the first 7 enemies.</ARA_Spawn_ARA_HiveCorvette_Rocket.description>
<ARA_Spawn_ARA_HiveCorvette_DiveBomb.label>Heavenly Shrine Cruise: Disaster Bombing</ARA_Spawn_ARA_HiveCorvette_DiveBomb.label>
<ARA_Spawn_ARA_HiveCorvette_DiveBomb.description>The Towing Type commands the Arachne Heavenly Shrine Beast Insect and attacks the target area with disaster missiles imbued with the Arachne Mic acid effect while sweeping through the battlefield at high speed.\n\nAlthough the cooldown of this support is much longer than other supports, its power is undeniable.</ARA_Spawn_ARA_HiveCorvette_DiveBomb.description>
<ARA_Spawn_ARA_HiveCorvette_Bombardment.label>Heavenly Shrine Cruise: Acid Bombing</ARA_Spawn_ARA_HiveCorvette_Bombardment.label>
<ARA_Spawn_ARA_HiveCorvette_Bombardment.description>The towing type commands the Arachne Heavenly Shrine Beast Insect, and slowly sweeps through the battlefield, dropping acid bombs with the Arachne Bug acid effect over a wide range of target areas.\n\nDuring flight, it uses a high-power, high-penetration Bloodrock Spiny Cannon to attack all enemies it encounters.</ARA_Spawn_ARA_HiveCorvette_Bombardment.description>
<ARA_Spawn_ARA_HiveCorvette_Strike.label>Heavenly Shrine Cruise: Bloodspine Surveillance</ARA_Spawn_ARA_HiveCorvette_Strike.label>
<ARA_Spawn_ARA_HiveCorvette_Strike.description>The Towing Type commands the Arachne Heavenly Shrine Beast Insect, and slowly sweeps through the battlefield, attacking all the enemies it encounters with its high-power, high-penetration Bloodrock Spiny Cannon.In this attack mode, the Heavenly Shrine Type's field of vision is narrow, making it difficult to aim at the entire enemy group.</ARA_Spawn_ARA_HiveCorvette_Strike.description>
</LanguageData>
