<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>

  <ARA_Queen_Upgrade_1_Stage.label>Queen species evolution - stage 1</ARA_Queen_Upgrade_1_Stage.label>
  <ARA_Queen_Upgrade_1_Stage.description>Cause the queen species to evolve internally and unlock the next level of Arachne eggs. \n\nNote: The Arachne eggs hatched after the Queen species evolve can still breed low-level Zerg, but the higher-level Arachne eggs are more sensitive to temperature.</ARA_Queen_Upgrade_1_Stage.description>
  <ARA_Queen_Upgrade_2_Stage.label>Queen species evolution - stage 2</ARA_Queen_Upgrade_2_Stage.label>
  <ARA_Queen_Upgrade_2_Stage.description>Cause the queen species to evolve internally and unlock the next level of Arachne eggs. \n\nNote: The Arachne eggs hatched after the Queen species evolve can still breed low-level Zerg, but the higher-level Arachne eggs are more sensitive to temperature.</ARA_Queen_Upgrade_2_Stage.description>
  <ARA_WeaponSmith_Upgrade_1_Stage.label>Craft Evolution - Stage 1</ARA_WeaponSmith_Upgrade_1_Stage.label>
  <ARA_WeaponSmith_Upgrade_1_Stage.description>Make the craft species evolve internally and unlock the next level of Arachne craft cocoon. \n\nNote: Unlike the evolution of the queen species, once the craft species evolves to the next stage, the Arachne craft cocoons hatched thereafter will no longer be able to produce equipment at the current stage and before. Moreover, the more advanced Arachne craft cocoons are, the more sensitive they are to temperature.</ARA_WeaponSmith_Upgrade_1_Stage.description>
  <ARA_WeaponSmith_Upgrade_2_Stage.label>Craft Evolution - Stage 2</ARA_WeaponSmith_Upgrade_2_Stage.label>
  <ARA_WeaponSmith_Upgrade_2_Stage.description>Make the craft species evolve internally and unlock the next level of Arachne craft cocoon. \n\nNote: Unlike the evolution of the queen species, once the craft species evolves to the next stage, the Arachne craft cocoons hatched thereafter will no longer be able to produce equipment at the current stage and before. Moreover, the more advanced Arachne craft cocoons are, the more sensitive they are to temperature.</ARA_WeaponSmith_Upgrade_2_Stage.description>
  <ARA_Myrmecocystus_Production_Medicine.label>Honeypot species conversion—Medicine Specialization</ARA_Myrmecocystus_Production_Medicine.label>
  <ARA_Myrmecocystus_Production_Medicine.description>Causes the honeypot species to undergo endogenous evolution at the expense of producing Arachne honey, allowing it to hatch medical cocoons and allow the use of medical abilities and manipulation of the phylogenetic species. \n\nThis evolutionary process is irreversible!</ARA_Myrmecocystus_Production_Medicine.description>
  <ARA_Myrmecocystus_Production_Fuel.label>Honeypot species conversion - flammable chamber</ARA_Myrmecocystus_Production_Fuel.label>
  <ARA_Myrmecocystus_Production_Fuel.description>Causes the honeypot species to undergo endogenous evolution, at the expense of producing Arachne honey, so that it can produce chemical fuel, enhance its armor, and give it the additional ability to shoot fire. \n\nThis evolutionary process is irreversible!</ARA_Myrmecocystus_Production_Fuel.description>
  <ARA_Fighter_Invisibility.label>Warrior Type Conversion - Invisible Killer</ARA_Fighter_Invisibility.label>
  <ARA_Fighter_Invisibility.description>Causes the warrior species to evolve internally, greatly impairing its ability to use long-range weapons and special skills in exchange for near-permanent invisibility and powerful melee capabilities. \n\nThis evolutionary process is irreversible!</ARA_Fighter_Invisibility.description>
  <ARA_Fighter_Genestealer.label>Warrior species conversion - gene thief</ARA_Fighter_Genestealer.label>
  <ARA_Fighter_Genestealer.description>The warrior species undergoes endogenous evolution, compromising its combat capabilities and ability to use skills, in exchange for the ability to steal genes from the enemy and inject genes into its own colonists. \n\nThis evolutionary process is irreversible!</ARA_Fighter_Genestealer.description>
  <ARA_Smokepop_Production_Bacterium.label>Mist species conversion——Jiu Bacteria Specialization</ARA_Smokepop_Production_Bacterium.label>
  <ARA_Smokepop_Production_Bacterium.description>Make the mist species undergo endogenous evolution, at the expense of spraying pheromones and reducing armor, so that it can regularly produce the advanced material of the Arachne Zerg - Activated Giant Bacteria. \n\nThis evolutionary process is irreversible!</ARA_Smokepop_Production_Bacterium.description>
  <ARA_Smokepop_Creeper.label>Mist seed conversion - Creep support</ARA_Smokepop_Creeper.label>
  <ARA_Smokepop_Creeper.description>Make the mist species undergo endogenous evolution, at the expense of ejecting pheromones, so that they can gain additional defense, movement speed, and the ability to lay mushroom carpets in a large area and at high speeds. \n\nThis evolutionary process is irreversible!</ARA_Smokepop_Creeper.description>
  <ARA_ShieldHead_Protector.label>Shieldhead Conversion—Hive Guard</ARA_ShieldHead_Protector.label>
  <ARA_ShieldHead_Protector.description>The shield-headed species undergo endogenous evolution, at the expense of its ability to produce chitin and build buildings, so that it can acquire more powerful combat capabilities, movement capabilities, and collision attack skills. \n\nThis evolutionary process is irreversible!</ARA_ShieldHead_Protector.description>
  <ARA_ShieldHead_HiveBuilder.label>Shieldhead Conversion - Master Builder</ARA_ShieldHead_HiveBuilder.label>
  <ARA_ShieldHead_HiveBuilder.description>This causes the shield-headed species to undergo endogenous evolution, allowing it to acquire more powerful chitin production capabilities and construction skills at the expense of its defense capabilities. \n\nThis evolutionary process is irreversible!</ARA_ShieldHead_HiveBuilder.description>
  <ARA_Skyraider_Hivelord.label>Transformation of Sky and Sky Species—Lord of Brood Insects</ARA_Skyraider_Hivelord.label>
  <ARA_Skyraider_Hivelord.description>The aerial species undergo endogenous evolution, at the cost of reduced mobility and loss of high-altitude maneuverability, allowing them to gain the ability to automatically project sky-nesting auxiliary insects at the enemy - these auxiliary insects are small in size and will cling to the enemy with annoying melee combat. \n\nThis evolutionary process is irreversible!</ARA_Skyraider_Hivelord.description>
  <ARA_Skyraider_Empthrower.label>Space-to-sky transformation - electromagnetic storm</ARA_Skyraider_Empthrower.label>
  <ARA_Skyraider_Empthrower.description>The aerospace species undergo endogenous evolution, at the cost of reduced mobility and loss of high-altitude maneuverability, allowing it to gain the ability to automatically project magnetic storm species auxiliary insects at the enemy - this auxiliary insect will release EMP in a suicide attack to fight against the mechanical race. \n\nThis evolutionary process is irreversible!</ARA_Skyraider_Empthrower.description>
  <ARA_Praetorian_Navigator.label>Guard species conversion—Pilot Lighthouse</ARA_Praetorian_Navigator.label>
  <ARA_Praetorian_Navigator.description>The guard species undergo endogenous evolution, sacrificing their shooting ability, jumping ability, and commanding ability in exchange for the ability to command aerial beasts and insects. \n\nThis evolutionary process is irreversible! Additionally, the Aerial Beast must be successfully airborne in order to be commanded - by the time you unlock this evolution path, the Aerial Beast should not be buildable yet.</ARA_Praetorian_Navigator.description>

</LanguageData>