<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
<ARA_Myrmecocystus_Production_Medicine.label>Honey can type conversion--medicine specialization</ARA_Myrmecocystus_Production_Medicine.label>
<ARA_Myrmecocystus_Production_Medicine.description>Internal evolution occurs in the honeycan species, making it possible to hatch medicinal cocoons at the cost of losing the ability to produce Arachne nectar, allowing for medical abilities and the manipulation of pseudo-thread species.\n\nThis evolutionary route does not yield Arachne insects.</ARA_Myrmecocystus_Production_Medicine.description>
<ARA_Myrmecocystus_Production_Fuel.label>Honey can type conversion——flammable chamber</ARA_Myrmecocystus_Production_Fuel.label>
<ARA_Myrmecocystus_Production_Fuel.description>Allows the Honey Can species to internally evolve, allowing them to produce chemical fuel at the cost of losing the ability to produce Arachne Honey. This strengthens their armor and also gives them the ability to shoot fire.\n\nThis evolution route does not yield Arachne Bugs.</ARA_Myrmecocystus_Production_Fuel.description>
<ARA_Myrmecocystus_Production_Dissolver.label>Honey can type conversion—strong acid decomposition</ARA_Myrmecocystus_Production_Dissolver.label>
<ARA_Myrmecocystus_Production_Dissolver.description>Allows the honeycan species to internally evolve and gain additional melting abilities, allowing them to release fat-dissolving acids on non-insect prisoners and slaves, causing them to continually lose body parts to produce nectar.\n\nThis evolutionary route does not yield any nectar.</ARA_Myrmecocystus_Production_Dissolver.description>
<ARA_Fighter_Invisibility.label>Warrior species conversion—hidden slayer</ARA_Fighter_Invisibility.label>
<ARA_Fighter_Invisibility.description>A warrior species undergoes an internal evolution, gaining near-permanent concealment and powerful melee combat abilities at the cost of losing the ability to use ranged weapons and special skills.\n\nThis evolutionary route does not yield lizards.</ARA_Fighter_Invisibility.description>
<ARA_Fighter_Genestealer.label>Warrior species conversion—gene thief</ARA_Fighter_Genestealer.label>
<ARA_Fighter_Genestealer.description>A warrior species undergoes internal evolution, gaining the ability to steal genes from enemies and transfer genes to colonists at the cost of losing combat ability and ability to use skills.\n\nThis evolutionary route does not yield worms.</ARA_Fighter_Genestealer.description>
<ARA_Smokepop_Production_Bacterium.label>Lost mist species conversion—Giant bacteria specialization</ARA_Smokepop_Production_Bacterium.label>
<ARA_Smokepop_Production_Bacterium.description>By causing the mist species to undergo internal evolution, at the cost of losing their pheromone injection ability and armor performance, they will be able to regularly produce the high-grade material of the Arachne insect class, ``Activated Giant Bacteria.''\n\nThis evolution route will not yield the Phyllis insects.</ARA_Smokepop_Production_Bacterium.description>
<ARA_Smokepop_Creeper.label>Lost fog species conversion——creep support</ARA_Smokepop_Creeper.label>
<ARA_Smokepop_Creeper.description>By causing a mist type to internally evolve, it loses its ability to eject pheromones, but gains defense power, movement speed, and the ability to deploy creep over a wide range and at high speed.\n\nWith this evolution route, you can obtain 6 Arachne Explosive type serpent insects.</ARA_Smokepop_Creeper.description>
<ARA_ShieldHead_Protector.label>Shieldhead species conversion--nest guardian</ARA_ShieldHead_Protector.label>
<ARA_ShieldHead_Protector.description>By causing the shield-head species to undergo internal evolution, they gain stronger combat power, mobility, and assault attack capabilities at the cost of losing their ability to produce shell elements and build.\n\nWith this evolution route, you can obtain 4 Arachneic acid-type caterpillars.</ARA_ShieldHead_Protector.description>
<ARA_ShieldHead_HiveBuilder.label>Shield head type conversion--Eikensha</ARA_ShieldHead_HiveBuilder.label>
<ARA_ShieldHead_HiveBuilder.description>By causing the shield-head species to undergo internal evolution, they gain stronger chitin production and building skills at the cost of losing their defensive abilities.\n\nThis evolutionary route will give you 4 Arachne-giant-jawed sycamores.</ARA_ShieldHead_HiveBuilder.description>
<ARA_Skyraider_Ferry.label>Sora Tensei Mutation - Transporter Bee</ARA_Skyraider_Ferry.label>
<ARA_Skyraider_Ferry.description>By causing an internal evolution in the sky type, the movement speed will be increased at the cost of losing the ability to maneuver at high altitudes, and when forming a caravan, the movement speed will be greatly increased.\n\nArachune sedges cannot be obtained with this evolution route.</ARA_Skyraider_Ferry.description>
<ARA_Skyraider_Empthrower.label>Sky type conversion—electromagnetic storm</ARA_Skyraider_Empthrower.label>
<ARA_Skyraider_Empthrower.description>By causing an internal evolution in the Sky-Celestial Type, at the cost of losing mobility and high-altitude maneuverability, it gains the ability to project Magneto-Violet Types of Breastworms - which release EMPs as a suicide attack to counter the Mechanoids.\n\nThis evolution route does not yield Arachne Breeders.</ARA_Skyraider_Empthrower.description>
<ARA_Skyraider_Hivelord.label>Sky Species Conversion——Lord of Nest Bugs</ARA_Skyraider_Hivelord.label>
<ARA_Skyraider_Hivelord.description>By causing an internal evolution in the Arachne Tensu species, you gain the ability to hatch a large number of Arachne Tensu species facilitators at the cost of reduced mobility and loss of high-altitude maneuverability.\n\nWith this evolution route, you can obtain eight Arachne Tensu species facilitators.</ARA_Skyraider_Hivelord.description>
<ARA_Praetorian_Navigator.label>Forbidden species conversion——Guiding light tower</ARA_Praetorian_Navigator.label>
<ARA_Praetorian_Navigator.description>By causing the Forbidden species to undergo internal evolution, they will gain the ability to command aerial beast insects at the cost of losing their shooting ability, jumping ability, and command ability.\n\nYou will not be able to obtain an Arachne insect with this evolution route.Please note that air beast insects will only be able to be commanded after successful takeoff - by the time this evolution path is released, you should not be able to build an aerial beast insect yet.</ARA_Praetorian_Navigator.description>
<ARA_Praetorian_Legion.label>Forbidden species conversion--The power of the army</ARA_Praetorian_Legion.label>
<ARA_Praetorian_Legion.description>By causing the Forbidden species to undergo internal evolution, at the cost of losing their command abilities, they gain stronger melee combat, long-range attack, and defense abilities, as well as the ability to counter enemies with physical techniques such as swinging their tails, charging, and jumping.\n\nArachne Osamu cannot be obtained through this evolution route.</ARA_Praetorian_Legion.description>
</LanguageData>
