<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>

  <ARA_Surgery_Install_Plasteel.label>Plasteel Shell Implantation</ARA_Surgery_Install_Plasteel.label>
  <ARA_Surgery_Install_Plasteel.description>Implants plasteel into the Arachnae's chitin shell. As the chitin continues to grow, the plasteel will be encased by the shell, forming a sturdier exoskeleton and enhancing the insectoid's defense.</ARA_Surgery_Install_Plasteel.description>
  <ARA_Surgery_Install_Plasteel.jobString>Performing targeted mutation.</ARA_Surgery_Install_Plasteel.jobString>

  <ARA_Plasteel_Shell_Hediff.label>Plasteel Shell</ARA_Plasteel_Shell_Hediff.label>
  <ARA_Plasteel_Shell_Hediff.description>The Arachnae gains enhanced defense from plasteel directly implanted into its chitin shell.</ARA_Plasteel_Shell_Hediff.description>

  <ARA_Plasteel_Shell.label>Plasteel Shell</ARA_Plasteel_Shell.label>
  <ARA_Plasteel_Shell.description>The Arachnae gains enhanced defense from plasteel directly implanted into its chitin shell. This operation does not require a crafted component and can be performed directly on an Arachnae overseer.</ARA_Plasteel_Shell.description>

  <ARA_Surgery_Install_Shell_Thorn.label>Shell Thorn Implantation</ARA_Surgery_Install_Shell_Thorn.label>
  <ARA_Surgery_Install_Shell_Thorn.description>Implants two rows of spine sacs into the Arachnae's shell. These are semi-autonomous organs that automatically fire spines at nearby enemies. This mutation also thickens the shell for stronger defense.</ARA_Surgery_Install_Shell_Thorn.description>
  <ARA_Surgery_Install_Shell_Thorn.jobString>Performing targeted mutation.</ARA_Surgery_Install_Shell_Thorn.jobString>

  <ARA_Shell_Thorn_Hediff.label>Shell Spines</ARA_Shell_Thorn_Hediff.label>
  <ARA_Shell_Thorn_Hediff.description>The Arachnae has two rows of spine sacs implanted on its shell. They automatically fire spines at nearby enemies unless the insectoid is engaged in melee combat.</ARA_Shell_Thorn_Hediff.description>

  <ARA_Shell_Thorn.label>Shell Spines</ARA_Shell_Thorn.label>
  <ARA_Shell_Thorn.description>Two rows of spine sacs are implanted on the Arachnae's shell. They automatically fire spines at nearby enemies unless the insectoid is engaged in melee combat. This operation does not require a crafted component and can be performed directly on an Arachnae overseer.</ARA_Shell_Thorn.description>

  <ARA_Surgery_Install_Reactive_Shell.label>Reactive Shell Implantation</ARA_Surgery_Install_Reactive_Shell.label>
  <ARA_Surgery_Install_Reactive_Shell.description>Implants a special reactive shell into the Arachnae's carapace. This shell is single-use and can pop off to block incoming damage, preventing harm to the insectoid's body.</ARA_Surgery_Install_Reactive_Shell.description>
  <ARA_Surgery_Install_Reactive_Shell.jobString>Performing targeted mutation.</ARA_Surgery_Install_Reactive_Shell.jobString>

  <ARA_Reactive_Shell_Hediff.label>Reactive Shell</ARA_Reactive_Shell_Hediff.label>
  <ARA_Reactive_Shell_Hediff.description>The Arachnae's reactive shell can protect it from one instance of external damage, but the shell fragment will then pop off, no longer providing defense.</ARA_Reactive_Shell_Hediff.description>

  <ARA_Reactive_Shell.label>Reactive Shell</ARA_Reactive_Shell.label>
  <ARA_Reactive_Shell.description>The Arachnae's reactive shell can protect it from one instance of external damage, but the shell fragment will then pop off, no longer providing defense. This operation does not require a crafted component and can be performed directly on an Arachnae overseer.</ARA_Reactive_Shell.description>

  <ARA_Surgery_Install_Carapace_Shell.label>Carapace Proliferation</ARA_Surgery_Install_Carapace_Shell.label>
  <ARA_Surgery_Install_Carapace_Shell.description>Thickens the Arachnae's carapace with chitin for additional defense.</ARA_Surgery_Install_Carapace_Shell.description>
  <ARA_Surgery_Install_Carapace_Shell.jobString>Performing targeted mutation.</ARA_Surgery_Install_Carapace_Shell.jobString>

  <ARA_Gene_Essence_Shell_Hediff.label>Carapace Proliferation</ARA_Gene_Essence_Shell_Hediff.label>
  <ARA_Gene_Essence_Shell_Hediff.description>The carapace of this Arachnae has been thickened with chitin, gaining additional defense.</ARA_Gene_Essence_Shell_Hediff.description>

  <ARA_Gene_Essence_Shell.label>Carapace Proliferation</ARA_Gene_Essence_Shell.label>
  <ARA_Gene_Essence_Shell.description>The Arachnae's carapace has been thickened with chitin, gaining additional defense. This operation does not require a crafted component and can be performed directly on an Arachnae overseer.</ARA_Gene_Essence_Shell.description>

  <ARA_Surgery_Install_Strengthening_Tendon.label>Strengthening Tendon Implantation</ARA_Surgery_Install_Strengthening_Tendon.label>
  <ARA_Surgery_Install_Strengthening_Tendon.description>Implants strengthening tendons into the Arachnae's legs, allowing the insectoid to move at higher speeds and gain the ability to make short-distance jumps.</ARA_Surgery_Install_Strengthening_Tendon.description>
  <ARA_Surgery_Install_Strengthening_Tendon.jobString>Performing targeted mutation.</ARA_Surgery_Install_Strengthening_Tendon.jobString>

  <ARA_Strengthening_Tendon_Hediff.label>Strengthening Tendons</ARA_Strengthening_Tendon_Hediff.label>
  <ARA_Strengthening_Tendon_Hediff.description>The Arachnae's strengthened tendons allow for high-speed movement and grant the ability to jump.</ARA_Strengthening_Tendon_Hediff.description>

  <ARA_Strengthening_Tendon.label>Strengthening Tendons</ARA_Strengthening_Tendon.label>
  <ARA_Strengthening_Tendon.description>The Arachnae's strengthened tendons allow for high-speed movement and grant the ability to jump. This operation does not require a crafted component and can be performed directly on an Arachnae overseer.</ARA_Strengthening_Tendon.description>

  <ARA_Surgery_Install_Slide_Patagium.label>Gliding Patagium Implantation</ARA_Surgery_Install_Slide_Patagium.label>
  <ARA_Surgery_Install_Slide_Patagium.description>Implants gliding patagia into the Arachnae's legs, allowing the insectoid to achieve extremely high speeds when moving on creep.</ARA_Surgery_Install_Slide_Patagium.description>
  <ARA_Surgery_Install_Slide_Patagium.jobString>Performing targeted mutation.</ARA_Surgery_Install_Slide_Patagium.jobString>

  <ARA_Slide_Patagium_Hediff.label>Gliding Patagium</ARA_Slide_Patagium_Hediff.label>
  <ARA_Slide_Patagium_Hediff.description>The gliding patagia on the Arachnae's legs allow for rapid movement on creep, but the bonus is immediately lost upon leaving the creep.</ARA_Slide_Patagium_Hediff.description>

  <ARA_Slide_Patagium.label>Gliding Patagium</ARA_Slide_Patagium.label>
  <ARA_Slide_Patagium.description>The gliding patagia on the Arachnae's legs allow for rapid movement on creep, but the bonus is immediately lost upon leaving the creep. This operation does not require a crafted component and can be performed directly on an Arachnae overseer.</ARA_Slide_Patagium.description>

  <ARA_Surgery_Install_Huge_Stomach.label>Auxiliary Stomach</ARA_Surgery_Install_Huge_Stomach.label>
  <ARA_Surgery_Install_Huge_Stomach.description>Induces a targeted mutation in the Arachnae, enlarging its nutrient-storing stomach pouch to hold more food.</ARA_Surgery_Install_Huge_Stomach.description>
  <ARA_Surgery_Install_Huge_Stomach.jobString>Performing targeted mutation.</ARA_Surgery_Install_Huge_Stomach.jobString>

  <ARA_Huge_Stomach_Hediff.label>Auxiliary Stomach</ARA_Huge_Stomach_Hediff.label>
  <ARA_Huge_Stomach_Hediff.description>The targeted mutation of the Arachnae grants it a larger stomach pouch to hold more nutrients.</ARA_Huge_Stomach_Hediff.description>

  <ARA_Huge_Stomach.label>Auxiliary Stomach</ARA_Huge_Stomach.label>
  <ARA_Huge_Stomach.description>The targeted mutation of the Arachnae grants it a larger stomach pouch to hold more nutrients. This operation does not require a crafted component and can be performed directly on an Arachnae overseer.</ARA_Huge_Stomach.description>

  <ARA_Surgery_Install_Cycle_Suppression.label>Life Cycle Suppression</ARA_Surgery_Install_Cycle_Suppression.label>
  <ARA_Surgery_Install_Cycle_Suppression.description>Induces a targeted mutation in the Arachnae, allowing it to live longer by removing the constraints of its natural lifespan. However, after injection with the life cycle suppressors, the insectoid will lose its self-healing ability.</ARA_Surgery_Install_Cycle_Suppression.description>
  <ARA_Surgery_Install_Cycle_Suppression.jobString>Performing targeted mutation.</ARA_Surgery_Install_Cycle_Suppression.jobString>

  <ARA_Cycle_Suppression_Hediff.label>Life Cycle Suppression</ARA_Cycle_Suppression_Hediff.label>
  <ARA_Cycle_Suppression_Hediff.description>The life cycle suppressors for the Arachnae prevent the insectoid's natural unconstrained growth to prolong its lifespan.</ARA_Cycle_Suppression_Hediff.description>

  <ARA_Cycle_Suppression.label>Life Cycle Suppression</ARA_Cycle_Suppression.label>
  <ARA_Cycle_Suppression.description>The life cycle suppressors for the Arachnae prevent the insectoid's natural unconstrained growth to prolong its lifespan. This operation does not require a crafted component and can be performed directly on an Arachnae overseer.</ARA_Cycle_Suppression.description>

  <ARA_Surgery_Install_Acidling_Pouch.label>Blaster Pouch</ARA_Surgery_Install_Acidling_Pouch.label>
  <ARA_Surgery_Install_Acidling_Pouch.description>Induces a targeted mutation in the Arachnae, pre-storing three about-to-hatch Arachnae Blasters in its pouch. Once released, they will attack the enemy in a suicidal assault.</ARA_Surgery_Install_Acidling_Pouch.description>
  <ARA_Surgery_Install_Acidling_Pouch.jobString>Performing targeted mutation.</ARA_Surgery_Install_Acidling_Pouch.jobString>

  <ARA_Acidling_Pouch_Hediff.label>Blaster Pouch</ARA_Acidling_Pouch_Hediff.label>
  <ARA_Acidling_Pouch_Hediff.description>The Arachnae's pouch contains several about-to-hatch Arachnae Blasters. They will immediately burst out and attack the enemy upon receiving a command.</ARA_Acidling_Pouch_Hediff.description>

  <ARA_Acidling_Pouch.label>Blaster Pouch</ARA_Acidling_Pouch.label>
  <ARA_Acidling_Pouch.description>The Arachnae's pouch contains several about-to-hatch Arachnae Blasters. They will immediately burst out and attack the enemy upon receiving a command. This operation does not require a crafted component and can be performed directly on an Arachnae overseer.</ARA_Acidling_Pouch.description>

  <ARA_Surgery_Install_Tumor_Pouch.label>Tumor Pouch</ARA_Surgery_Install_Tumor_Pouch.label>
  <ARA_Surgery_Install_Tumor_Pouch.description>Induces a targeted mutation in the Arachnae, pre-storing a fading tumor in its pouch. Once released, it will convert a large area of the ground into creep terrain.</ARA_Surgery_Install_Tumor_Pouch.description>
  <ARA_Surgery_Install_Tumor_Pouch.jobString>Performing targeted mutation.</ARA_Surgery_Install_Tumor_Pouch.jobString>

  <ARA_Tumor_Pouch_Hediff.label>Tumor Pouch</ARA_Tumor_Pouch_Hediff.label>
  <ARA_Tumor_Pouch_Hediff.description>The Arachnae's pouch contains a fading tumor. Once released, it will convert a large area of the ground into creep terrain.</ARA_Tumor_Pouch_Hediff.description>

  <ARA_Tumor_Pouch.label>Tumor Pouch</ARA_Tumor_Pouch.label>
  <ARA_Tumor_Pouch.description>The Arachnae's pouch contains a fading tumor. Once released, it will convert a large area of the ground into creep terrain. This operation does not require a crafted component and can be performed directly on an Arachnae overseer.</ARA_Tumor_Pouch.description>

  <ARA_CureAcid.label>Neutralize Neurotoxin</ARA_CureAcid.label>
  <ARA_CureAcid.description>The Arachnae swarm can use healing serum to neutralize the effects of the Arachnae neurotoxin, allowing the victim to recover.</ARA_CureAcid.description>
  <ARA_CureAcid.jobString>Neutralizing neurotoxin.</ARA_CureAcid.jobString>
  <ARA_CureAcid.successfullyRemovedHediffMessage>{0} successfully neutralized Arachnae neurotoxin in {1}.</ARA_CureAcid.successfullyRemovedHediffMessage>

  <ARA_CureBloodRot.label>Clear Nematode Infection</ARA_CureBloodRot.label>
  <ARA_CureBloodRot.description>Clears the Arachnae Mimic Nematode infection from the patient using a combination of drugs and targeted therapy. This is a very complex operation and can only be performed with glitterworld medicine.</ARA_CureBloodRot.description>
  <ARA_CureBloodRot.jobString>Clearing nematode infection.</ARA_CureBloodRot.jobString>
  <ARA_CureBloodRot.successfullyRemovedHediffMessage>{0} successfully cleared the nematode infection in {1}.</ARA_CureBloodRot.successfullyRemovedHediffMessage>

</LanguageData>